What's up?
Hold on, I gotta blow my nose.
I haven't spoken at all today, and I just realized as soon as I spoke... that my nose was filled with snot.
There we go.
It's done.
What's up?
Are you ready for some Minecraft?
My mods are telling me that you guys have been misbehaving.
So I want to make something clear.
Please don't spoil me, okay?
If it takes 50 years for me to figure something out, so be it.
I will figure things out in time, okay?
I'm having a blast enjoying this at my own pace.
I don't need anyone telling me how to play the game or what to do next or what I've missed, alright?
That's very important.
So please don't tell me what to do.
I understand you love the game and you want me to experience all the things.
But if you tell me the solution to something or tell me what to do next, you're actually robbing me of that experience.
So you're actually making it worse for me.
You're making my experience worse.
I just want to get that out of the way, okay?
Now you're free to sit there and talk about spoilers while I'm playing because I'm not looking at chat while I'm playing.
But don't try to spoil me in the beginning of the stream or at the end or during the breaks when I talk to chat, okay?
Nobody spoiled anything.
It's just that the mods have been working overtime, apparently.
Deleting comments and all that, you know?
Just... please don't.
Okay.
Now that we got that out of the way...
Are you ready?
For some Minecraft.
Today is a great day.
I shall be cranking it indeed.
I shall be cranking it manually, automatically, and semantically.
The crank shall crank.
Just like you guys are cranking the wheels right now.
Oh, look at that!
It's almost a genuine animation that is playing continuously.
I love when it's just spinning like that.
You know what makes me really sad?
When those gears are not spinning.
When they're just sitting there, you know?
That's actually the worst thing ever.
And especially on a Friday, you can't let those gears just sit there.
Making it look like they're lagging.
Which they're not!
They're spinning!
How you guys doing?
Are you having a good Friday?
What kind of plants you got?
What are you eating for dinner?
I need dinner inspiration.
Because I haven't decided yet.
I was thinking of being naughty and eating something very nasty, but...
Maybe not.
I like that people are just saying food.
Pasta.
Pizza.
Bacon.
What is monkey bread?
I don't know what that is.
Boiled eggs and toast chicken.
That sounds pretty good.
There's a Tom Yum noodles.
Hey, that's an instant noodle, right?
I've never had those.
Monkey bread is good.
But what is monkey bread?
Is it like...
Hold on.
Let me figure it out.
Monkey bread.
Oh!
That looks so American.
What the hell?
That's like a cake.
That's not bread.
That's a freaking cake.
This one.
Good.
Now we have sound.
Can you hear this?
I think you can.
Oh!
And immediately the music starts as well.
After logging in.
That is incredible.
Oh, I got some lags.
Let me just let everything load in here.
Okay.
So last time I had a bit of an unfortunate incident.
I know I said I was sort of rage quitting out of it after that.
I wasn't.
It was time to stop anyway.
It was okay.
I didn't really lose much anyway.
Okay, it is safe.
I was about to say, am I gonna do the same thing again now?
But no, I removed the fire.
It's all good.
Imagine.
Imagine if I had jumped in again.
That wouldn't have been the greatest start.
Oh yeah, I have my checklist over here too.
What was on that?
Oh, this one is done.
Yeah, that's why it's checked.
Wool.
I think we got most of that, but I still want to leave it.
Andesides.
We gotta find a better way to get andesides.
We really do.
What was I doing anyway?
So I was doing this weird...
Blasting.
But I had another plan at the time.
Oh yeah.
I'm gonna be blasting my cows, dude.
Why are they all...
clumped up over there?
What's happening?
What's so exciting over here?
Maybe they're trying to...
Maybe their AI is trying to get out via this tree and they can't.
Is that what's happening?
I cannot get out.
It is illegal.
By the way, I had an idea for the roof of my house.
And it's something that I wanted to do...
in the last season of Minecraft, but I never managed to fully realize the vision.
I'm not gonna reveal what it is yet.
But it's kind of exciting.
It gets me going, you know?
Today we're definitely making some more house.
So that means more wood.
And...
Oh, right!
I keep coming back to this.
I wanted to make the floor out of the goddamn andesite thingy.
Let me see here.
Andesite...
Wait, what if I make the floor out of andesite table cover?
Is that crazy?
Ah, that's crazy!
Don't do that.
That's insane.
Also, the only way to make what I need is to actually chop a wood manually and then, you know, applied manually afterwards.
So, not great.
But is there a way I know of to not do that?
Automated shapeless crafting?
No, that's to make depot.
I mean, I could do it fast, I guess.
I have a lot of wood.
It's not really that big of a deal.
I just need to...
Get going, you know?
I need to just do it.
Instead of sitting here whining.
Yeah, let's do it.
Let's just do it.
I also have some alloy.
Alloy.
Somewhere.
I should have it.
Oh, did I lose that last time?
Ah, I may have lost it.
In the, uh, blasting incident.
Ah, shit.
Alloy.
Zinc nuggets and andesite.
Or iron nuggets, either words.
Andesite.
I don't think I have that either.
Actually.
Oh!
Look at that!
Why did I put it in here?
I also have this in here.
Oh, shit!
Okay, hold on.
We gotta put this in here instead.
Otherwise, I'll confuse myself.
There we go.
Mechanical saw.
I am actually gonna bring that.
I'm also gonna crank it.
Cause I need to get more wood.
Um...
Zinc.
Oh no, we need andesite first.
Right!
That's the thing I needed to go get a lot of.
Andesite.
But, guys, here's the thing.
We can't get a lot of andesite until we have a good pickaxe.
And we can't get a good pickaxe until we have a lot of...
enchantments.
And we can't get enchantments without books.
And we can't get books without having found the hotel.
So today we're finding a hotel.
And what else?
Getting levels.
Why am I level one?
Oh no!
The blasting incident set us back ten years.
Aw sh...
Okay, so we gotta go level up as well.
That's fine.
And...
What else do I need to enchant my pickaxe?
That's it, right?
Oh!
Of course I need to find a...
recipe for it.
No, I need to get lucky with it.
That's right.
I need levels.
I need books.
That's it pretty much.
Levels and books.
So, we're going on an adventure.
Which means this is gonna have to wait.
Actually keep the dirt.
Half of it.
Toolbox obviously comes with me.
I don't know if I should bring the crank for this.
I don't think so actually.
I'm leaving the crank at home.
Hmm.
I'm not going...
chopping down wood, you know.
New shield for sure.
So that means a little bit of iron.
And some wood.
Let's throw the other one away.
Like that.
May have to make another axe.
This one is getting a little worn.
Ah, but do I...
I do have diamonds.
Fantastic.
Axe.
That needs sticks.
I can make it.
Maybe I have it.
I don't have it.
I'm gonna keep this until it runs out.
And then I'll, you know.
Yeah.
That's the plan.
Shovel!
Of course.
I think I lost that in the blasting incident.
You stay here as well.
This is getting a little full, I understand.
Toolbox.
We need a bit of wood.
Just standard wood.
Clipboard.
For emergencies.
I really gotta make that checklist.
Did I lose my other clipboard in the incident?
No, it's in here.
Let's make another clipboard.
What does it take?
Alloy paper planks.
I think I used my last paper.
But I can make paper out of...
Something.
Sugar cane.
I don't have any.
Shit.
Can I not make the...
Can I not turn books into paper?
Somehow?
Sandpaper.
Kinda wanna make that too, but...
Not yet.
Oh, we need food.
Way more food.
Where is all my food?
Didn't I used to have a million food?
Also, 23 books.
Oh yeah, it's gonna take a lot.
A lot more than what I have.
Let's make a book.
It's paper and leather.
Leather I have.
So, honestly...
We gotta find...
You know what?
I'm actually bringing this.
Let's change this list.
Sugar cane.
Wasn't it?
Sugar cane?
Yeah.
Sugar cane.
Andesite.
Books.
I mean, if we can, of course.
Let's just put that along with sugar cane.
And then I need to find experience.
That's...
A given.
And...
That's pretty much it, I think.
Yeah.
A bucket!
Maybe we bring a bucket.
That's actually...
Great.
But what about this lava?
How do I store this?
Cauldron, right?
Iron ingot.
I will store this lava.
Hopefully it's not gonna, you know, burn down my shit.
While I'm gone.
There we go!
Sick.
Now we have that.
Some more torches, perhaps.
But I think I ran out of coal.
Oh, coal!
That's a good one.
Coal.
And...
We can fill this out as we go.
But yeah.
Right now, let's just...
Move on.
And obviously we gotta be able to find our way back, too.
Expedition has begun.
And look at this.
Immediately.
Oh!
Wait, wait, wait!
Something else I need to get.
Diamonds.
Because I need to get a full diamond suit today.
That needs to happen.
Can't be running around in iron armor anymore.
Uh, speak enough!
Hold on!
We don't even have armor!
Jesus Christ!
Also, maybe I'll bring my diving suit.
Could be a good idea.
Need, uh, armor and chest...
No, chest and legs.
There we go.
And...
Ah, wait a minute.
You know what?
I'm actually gonna do this in an efficient way.
I'm not gonna bring my helmet and boots.
That's right.
I'm leaving these.
Just to free up space, you know?
These still have armor on them, so...
It's not that bad.
And I look kinda cool.
Ah, but that means I also leave the chest behind.
That's six armor.
Four.
Okay, it's not too bad!
I can...
I can survive for sure.
Yeah.
Definitely need to kill some animals.
Oh!
Let's go to bed first.
Uh, we can do that as we go.
I have a bed with me.
So now we can survive underwater too.
Could actually be the ideal place to farm some...
AndeAndesite or...
Diamonds.
If we find a nice underwater cave.
No fear of getting killed, you know?
Let me see if I see something actually.
Hey, look at that little island with a tree on it.
We should have a little bonfire on that one or something.
Oh, wait a minute.
This is one of those...
Aren't there chests here?
Or am I thinking of something else?
The problem is I have to take these off every time I want to go up.
It's gonna get a little annoying.
Okay.
So the question is, where do I go first?
Let me see my clipboard.
I mean, it would make sense to do...
No, let's just explore.
Who knows, maybe we'll find a hotel.
Right now I'm just going north.
North, north, north.
And there's gonna be a big ocean on the other Andesite.
We're just gonna cross that.
I don't care.
Oh, and lots of sugarcane on the way.
That's wonderful.
Let's quickly go to bed.
Wait.
I need to let them burn.
I'll grab these.
Oh man, I really don't like that.
Now we can grab this over here.
Why is this guy... Oh, he's in water.
Hmm.
Oh, wait!
I lost my bow!
That's actually kind of horrible.
I don't mind some combat, actually.
I need experience.
Oh, shit.
No!
I mean...
Okay.
I'll do some mining.
The annoying thing is, when you mine on the water, everything sort of goes up instead of down.
That's gonna make it weird.
Hmm.
It's also super dark down here.
Yeah.
If I go down here, I need a potion of...
I was about to say visibility.
What's it called?
Night vision.
Leave me alone.
I'm gonna skirt the outAndesite of this.
This is very memorable.
I will not forget this part.
Oh yeah, and this island too.
Let me actually just do this.
Just in case.
I'm gonna keep doing it here.
And now the thing is, I just wanna go north.
I wanna find a whole new land, you know?
Like that!
That's a whole new land.
Last time I went here, and then I went back to this island, and then I went back sorta.
So we're gonna do it in a new way.
Those look like new blocks, the ones in between there.
But I could be wrong.
And when I say new blocks, I mean like with the create mod, right?
Ooh, let's go loot that box.
A portal discovered.
I feel like I haven't seen many of these.
I've been unlucky with that.
What is that?
Wait!
Is that, uh, crystals?
I think it is.
Just give me everything.
Wait, what?
Oh!
I got, uh, gold nuggets.
That's what's happening.
Let me see here.
Fortune 3!
Fortune 1.
Curse of... I don't like...
Honestly, I don't even know what Curse of Vanishing is.
I have no idea what that does!
It's been a mystery since day one.
Also, we need to stick to north.
But maybe my, um...
Fortune 3 can...
help me with something.
I wonder what though.
So, it's mostly stuff like gravel.
Ehh...
It's not gonna help me much.
What is that?
ANOTHER portal!
There...
I thought that was a portal too.
Oh, but that's a ship!
That's a ship over there.
The first one I've seen.
Doesn't look like a continent.
More like an island.
But I'll explore it.
Imagine if there was a hotel on this island.
That would be so cool actually.
Just on an island, you know?
I don't know what is happening with this.
Like, why does that happen?
Randomly in certain spots.
It's so weird.
Hey, dolphins!
Too bad they can't give me speed while I'm on the boat.
Turn me into a speed boat.
Oh, wait!
I just got a black screen.
Uh, I need to turn off some software in the background.
Hold on.
I know what's causing it.
There we go.
Oh no.
No!
The game fucking crashed!
Okay.
That software does not play nice with Minecraft.
I can tell you that.
Don't ever run Apollo while playing Minecraft.
Don't do it.
It's like the only game that has a problem with it.
It's crazy.
Okay.
Load it up.
There we go.
Please tell me it's saved.
Nice.
Good.
I'm gonna grab this.
Nice.
Thank you.
Dude, I can't not see this as some kind of...
graphical bug.
Reminds me of the source engine, you know?
When there's a texture missing.
It looks like that to me.
It is not at all a mushroom, in my opinion.
Oh, nice.
Obsidian.
Protection too.
Fire protection!
Mmm.
Very nice.
Dude, this portal is pretty much done!
Should we go in?
We've got the obsidian!
Maybe we take a quick peek.
Just a quick peek.
I just wanna see.
Okay.
Oh, wait.
Who's cutting onions?
Maybe...
Oh, maybe that one will unlock new stuff for us.
I don't actually want this.
Maybe I'll keep it.
No!
No.
I can always get some.
Grab this.
I should put on some gold, of course.
And...
There we go.
Yep.
Here we go.
Oh, wait, wait, wait!
Uh, bed.
There we go.
Just in case.
Nice!
That's amazing.
Wait, I need a hole for this.
Where the hell am I?
Oh!
What was that?
Um...
No, never mind.
Hmm...
Oh!
I thought I was falling down!
Uh, you know what?
I'm actually gonna leave.
But it's good to know that this is here.
I may actually put a little list.
Or a little sign.
We don't want granite.
Um...
You see all this?
Okay, check this out.
This is my plan now.
The exploration setup.
Arrow.
Bone.
Uh, what else is common and annoying?
Maybe this?
Gosh, I don't know.
What else is really annoying?
Coal, maybe?
A little annoying.
Definitely a little annoying.
Gold.
I mean, we can turn these into this if we have enough of it, so...
Don't really need these swords.
But I can disenchant them, so I do need them.
Obsidian.
Don't want the fire charge.
Don't care.
Flint...
I already have flint and steel.
Good.
I'm happy.
I'm not gonna make a sign.
But I will put down a little...
Doop!
Just like that.
Very cool entrance there.
There's probably some good shit.
I'll explore that later.
The idea today is to get powerful.
Armor.
Enchantments.
That's the first thing.
Nothing.
I can't just dismiss islands either.
I need to sort of see.
Who knows, maybe there's a hotel hiding right over here.
Watch.
Hotel in three.
No, I'm kidding.
I imagine though.
Imagine.
I feel like I would have seen it too.
It's kind of big, right?
Ah.
Hold up a minute.
I kind of need...
Oh.
Even if I find a hotel.
I need to pick it up and take it with me.
And I don't have that.
Otherwise I'm just gonna create...
Books.
But I guess it's not that bad to create books.
It's still a decent thing.
This is very beachy.
I should take some sand.
Yeah.
Let's take a bunch of sand.
Make some glass.
Because I have some ideas regarding the house and glass.
I think those ideas are obvious.
Given the plan with it.
Then again.
You would rather have some speed on the...
On the shovel as well.
Before you do that, right?
I can take a little bit.
What is that sound I'm hearing?
Oh, it's you?
What's up, bro?
Okay.
One, two, three.
That's one stack.
Sleep.
So far so good.
And I have only been going north.
So it's super easy to go back.
In case I need to.
I came from here.
Yep.
We go this way now.
I have good feelings about this continent.
You'll see what I mean.
You ready?
I keep expecting a hotel to pop up at any moment, you know?
I actually wonder how rare they are.
I mean, I've seen my fair share of them, but...
How actually rare are they?
And who knows?
Maybe I was lucky or unlucky.
Oh, one thing I should be doing...
Oh, I should have brought some bottles.
In case I need to collect honey from bees.
See, that would have been smart.
Like that.
Oh.
I gotta make more torches as well.
Which means this.
Oh, I don't like that sound in my ear.
Thanks.
Wait, uh...
I got lost.
Where the hell is the sun?
It's already up there?!
What the fuck?
I thought it was near the horizon.
Man, time is moving fast.
Also, where are my cows at?
No, it's a small island!
Watch.
Maybe not the smartest idea, because I took damage, but you know.
It was cool.
Oh, wait, wait.
I should be putting down a torch.
Just to play it safe.
What is that over there?
Oh, it's nothing.
That looks intriguing, doesn't it?
Is that jungle?
Something's going on there.
I'm not sure.
Oh, let's steer clear of that.
I hate when these guys FaceTime me.
Whatever it's called.
That's a nice mountain.
Reminds me of that mountain from Lord of the Rings.
With the horse lords, you know?
In the center of the valley.
Slightly.
Okay, we gotta go north.
I'm already veering off course.
This was where I was, actually.
I should be going this way.
Weird flowers.
Cows!
I need you!
Oh, there's a lot of cows here.
Wonderful.
Oh, massive mountain.
Massive mountain.
Maybe I'll get an elytra today, actually.
Just so we can explore easier.
That means we gotta find Enderman.
We need to murder him.
Let's have one torch here.
What is that?
Oh.
It looked purple on my screen in the distance.
And purple means hotel, right?
So, I thought, hotel.
I'm tempted to go up there and kill those cows.
Ah, you know what?
Ooh!
Look at that!
Beautiful area.
I may go there after.
I just wanna go up here and take a look around, you know?
From a high vantage point.
Also got sheep.
I need to kill those for wool.
Actually quite important.
Do I even need to jump?
I don't!
Nice.
Oh my god, there are so many here.
Dude!
Why are there so many animals?
We got black...
Wait, we just unlocked some new stuff?
Ah, just black colored items, I guess.
Thank you.
Okay, on the cows, we do need to jump.
One shot them.
Good.
You're coming with me.
You're not going anywhere.
You shall die.
Hiding up here, eh?
Eh, a village!
Sweet!
Dude, there's all kinds of stuff here.
It's actually amazing.
Ah, but I can't get too lost.
Where did I... oops.
Torch down there.
Okay, lava.
South.
Am I seeing anything?
It's a weirdly, uh, Swiss-looking mountain over there.
Very cool.
Well, we got the landmarks established.
If these guys have a smoker, I may steal it.
Just to smoke my meat.
I have a lot of it.
Also, my inventory is utter crap.
Again.
I actually don't want the black wool.
Taking up inventory space.
Don't want this either.
Or that.
Man, that is a massive area with pink trees.
I don't think I've ever seen something that massive.
There's also a village up there.
There.
Very cool.
Oh, yeah?
Jumping on the beds.
Ooh.
Oh, shit!
I need to grow potatoes, dude!
Yeah!
Oh, we can, uh, fan them.
Wait, what?
I can make rotten potatoes?
What's up with that?
I'll take this bed.
I'd rather have the golden one.
Man, I love these simple designs!
Fuck, I need to make something like this, you know?
Simple entrance.
Oh, it's like a looming house.
They be looming here.
Honestly, even if we don't find a hotel, I've gotten so much sugar cane already.
I think I'm chilling.
It don't even matter.
Oh, I should maybe have brought some...
money.
Just in case we find like a crazy...
deal here on an enchantment.
I forgot what the enchanter dudes look like.
Like a priest or something, I think.
Hey!
Yeah!
Sick.
And then I don't need these anymore.
What you got in here?
Oh!
You got three diamonds?!
Thank you!
I'm even gonna take this from you.
No, I'm not.
You get to keep that.
I took your money, so it's only fair that you get to keep the rest.
Ooh, you built your village right next to a cave, huh?
I like your style.
I do the same at home.
Got a cat over there.
No fish, unfortunately.
Haven't even had a single fishing rod yet.
It needs to happen soon.
There's probably some...
ingredients or recipes involving fish or...
stuff from the ocean, you know?
I'm thinking...
like the coral thing.
Or whatever.
The spiral.
Rock.
Crustacean.
You know what I mean?
The one that has a yellow text.
I think.
We should sleep.
Cheers.
Alright!
Let's move on!
I'm going on this mountain now.
Nice.
Gotta get all the recipes.
But I'm not actually interested in the...
stuff from it.
So I just basically killed it for the recipe only.
Oh, I should go on that mountain though.
So that's where I came from right there.
Right over there I have torches.
I am not lost.
I'm actually...
very precisely where I know where I am.
You know what I mean?
And it's not even approximately.
It is exactly.
Torch.
And another one on the other Andesite.
For good measure.
It doesn't even feel like a mountain.
This feels like a whole ass...
flat terrain.
In any case, this will be easy to remember.
You know?
On the way back.
What's up guys?
Maybe it's time to go caving.
Because we do need...
diamonds.
I think we got coal at this point.
Sugar cane is also pretty much done at this point.
But more is good.
But you know...
We reached the bare minimum that we needed.
When I find a really nice cave, then I'm gonna go in and look for diamonds.
But the thing is, some biomes have more diamonds than others.
So, you know, you go into a cave and...
you just see like a lot of diamonds.
And you know this is a good spot for diamonds, right?
Ah!
I messed it up!
Man, show me a hotel!
Actually, hold on.
Do I even want to enter a hotel?
That place is frickin' scary.
I'm gonna get murdered.
Maybe I should focus on diamond armor first, and then hotel.
But then again, I mean, we gotta find a hotel.
Before we can do anything.
Hey guys!
Oh yeah!
I can make such a big windmill when I come home.
In fact, I need to make a bigger one because...
we have an achievement for that.
Nether?
Why is the nether over there?
Shouldn't that be over here?
Assemble a windmill of maximum strength.
I still haven't...
Oh!
Superglue some blocks into a group.
Yeah, but I don't know how to do that.
Yet.
I think I know.
But I need to find...
Ayyy!
I need to find a swamp!
Let's... okay.
Look for swamp.
Because we need to kill green guys.
In fact, we need it for different things.
Have you killed too many cows?
45 raw beef?
That's a lot.
You get to live.
I will never lag for leather either.
So that's...
You know what?
This is actually perfect for making books.
Okay, we've got another mountain.
I think that looks like a hotel.
Okay, we really need to make an oven now.
So...
We gotta find stone.
Stone, and then we're gonna have to smoke.
Uh...
Smoker...
What does that take?
I don't know.
Let me see.
Oh, easy.
Okay.
We just need stone, pretty much.
I'm gonna take four of these.
So I'm ready.
Let's get up there.
I'm gonna put a torch on that mountain up there.
Hey, that's a nice looking tree!
Look at that one!
That's a very nice tree!
I wonder if I can take a screenshot of it while I'm looking at it with the zoom.
Nice.
For the memory books.
Hup!
More pink trees!
Dude, what is this area?
Okay, let's get the stone!
I think I need...
Yeah, that's enough.
Furnace...
Smoker...
Fur smoke!
And then we...
Ah!
We're gonna sit here while it's raining!
Cook that beef!
And while that's doing that, we're gonna collect more of this.
Make sure no monsters spawn on us.
Man, how cozy is this?
I kinda wanna do this in real life, you know?
Mine coal while my beef is cooking.
While I'm inAndesite a cave, taking shelter from the rain.
That's Minecraft.
In fact, you know what?
I'm gonna optimize the shit out of this.
Watch.
This is insane.
I'm going full smoker mode.
Tree, I need you.
Wait, did I actually leave some birch behind back there?
Did I...
Did I leave a crime?
I feel like I took four birch and then I left the rest?
I hope not.
Oh god, I hope not.
Um...
Give me half.
In.
Okay, that's cooking nicely.
While that's cooking, let me take a look up here real quick.
Snow!
Okay.
Let's bring back some snow.
Exciting.
More materials is good.
22 stakes now.
Oh yeah.
Looking real good.
I don't actually want this.
Kinda regret bringing the diving stuff.
Let me see here.
I technically don't need this obsidian either.
Leather is definitely one of these things, right?
Annoying things.
What else is annoying?
Well, not that much until I kill more monsters.
We can turn this into things.
Two of them.
Nine ironnoggers?
Isn't that...
Yep.
Sure is...
Could even cook some iron if I wanted.
Like, you may think, why does he need apples?
I need them because...
Uh, you can turn them into golden apples, right?
I forgot how, but you can do that.
Nice, so that's all done.
Half.
Golden nuggets.
I don't actually want those strays.
Get them away from me.
White wool is kind of annoying.
Um...
You know what?
I'm just gonna use this until it runs out.
Fuck it.
Cuz I don't really...
I'm not gonna use it anyway.
You know, I have to just use it.
Makes more sense.
Guess we can put this in here too.
Now, while that's doing that...
Torches!
I need more.
Great.
Hey, I can make another clipboard now.
Is that because I have a clipboard?
Or what?
Wait, why is that?
Why can't I click on it?
That's weird.
Wait a second.
Shears.
Maybe it's better to just shear the sheep instead of killing them.
Cuz I'm not interested in muttons anyway.
I'm really not.
Yeah, I don't care.
Let's go to bed.
Also, I can't forget to drink before my ice cubes melt.
Oh, don't go that way.
Oh, no.
Okay, keep going north.
We're going towards the snow.
Uh, put the sticks here.
Now I can instantly remove the leaves from trees as well.
You know what?
Why not?
Bring it on then, suckers.
Kill each other!
Yeah!
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Oh, there we go!
There we go!
I'm just gonna eat my snacks while I look at you.
Come on, guys!
Who's gonna win?
This guy's gonna win!
Terrible prediction.
Fucking attack, children!
He's so tiny, hard to hit!
Good experience!
Solid!
Let's see if this is a promising cave for diamonds.
No, it's not.
It's a very unpromising cave.
Also called a disappointing cave.
Is that actually the opposite of...
Disappointment.
Oh!
Whoops.
I don't like that.
We can't just have a random path.
Right?
But watch this.
We're going to do...
Oh!
I thought I could double dip!
Oh, man.
Okay.
Too bad.
Shit.
No, don't pick up...
Somehow my inventory is crap again.
What happened?
Why is it bad?
Okay, you know what?
Do we need the sand?
Yeah, we need the sand.
We do this.
See, Rotten Flesh is annoying.
That's very annoying.
That goes in here.
Sugar cane is also kind of annoying.
I don't need obsidian.
Away you go.
I forgot what I put in there.
Diamonds?
Okay.
Yo, this is a very hilly landscape here.
Mountainous, even.
I need to see what's on this Andesite first.
There better be something good.
Okay.
We got big boy trees back there.
Tall boys.
Village.
What is this place, man?
Why is it so not flat?
That guy forgot to wipe himself.
Look at his butt.
Ew.
Why is it so...
spotty?
Ew.
That
looks kind of exciting.
Man, I wish I could fly.
Imagine just soaring down there right now.
This is why I need to get a lighter today.
But I just don't see any Enderman.
Where's the Enderman?
The problem is, if I jump down, then I'm gonna lose sight of where I am.
I need to stay up high.
Also, we are getting kind of far away from home, I'm aware.
Maybe it's time to soon call it, you know?
And start heading back before we get too lost.
And if I go caving now, it could actually be really bad.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I love that sound!
Snip, snip, snip.
Thank you, guys.
Not too intrigued by what I'm seeing here.
Let me snip you.
Wait, does that give me more?
Wait a sec.
Not only does it leave them alive, it actually gives me more wool.
Wow.
That's crazy, man.
Okay, I'm gonna go back.
I think I'm too far away from home.
But maybe I'll take a little scenic route back.
So instead of going straight that way, I'm going sort of...
like that.
In a parabola.
And trust me, it's a good idea.
You know why?
Let me snip you.
Did I just get three?!
No, that's two.
Don't need eggs.
Yeah, fuck it.
Sprint time.
We're going home.
You know what I need to do?
I need to make an airplane.
And then I go explore.
The thing is though, I don't know how to make an airplane.
Maybe it's easier to get a lighter than it is to make an airplane.
I'm not sure.
But I'm gonna try for sure.
That would be the way, right?
Man, if I die here, I'm actually kind of screwed.
Imagine I fall down and die right here.
What do I do?
Like there's no way I'm gonna find this corpse.
That would be bad.
That's why I'm playing so carefully.
Oh, pink trees.
You know what?
Let's do the parabola but on the other Andesite.
This way.
Because there's pink trees on that Andesite and I want to see what's up there.
I just want to see the view.
Lots of birch here.
So I wonder, with my house I currently use dark oak, right?
I was conAndesitering maybe I mix and match some different wood types.
Like oak or even birch or spruce.
Something like that.
I'm definitely decided on the floor though.
That's gonna be the anticide stuff.
But that one is harder...
to make than you may think.
I mean, you have to do it manually, right?
No!
Ah!
Fuck.
I thought it were just a...
Damn it.
Take me up.
That was bad.
Embarrassing.
It's okay though.
What's up, chickens?
I mean...
Uh...
Pigs!
Why the...
At first I was like, chickpeas, but no, that's...
It's chickens.
And then I realized...
I am wrong.
I forgot the word for a second.
That's a chicken.
I know my chickens.
Okay, man, look at that mountain though!
It's crying!
We're gonna call this mountain Isaac.
His eyes.
Right there.
It's beautiful.
Oh, should I sleep?
Yeah.
Play it safe.
I think my no death...
Uh...
Promise is...
Dude, it looked like a pegasus.
From a distance.
Because they were merged together?
Or one of those things from Harry Potter, you know?
The ones that...
He flies on.
I was like, what is that...
Thing?
Is that a mod?
You know?
But it wasn't.
Snip!
That's just one.
Three!
Man, you're hairy.
Wow.
Hairy sheep.
You're a sheep, Hattie!
I'm a what?
You're a sheep.
I'm a meh!
Sorry, I'm a little silly today.
The silly mood prevails.
Oh!
Look at that tower!
Let's fuck him up.
That's where they're hiding out.
Unfortunately, they didn't bring a bow.
I see one over there already.
Hey!
What's going on, brother?
Oh.
He kinda fainted me there.
Dude, they kinda hurt.
Oh my god.
Oh, there's more.
They have lava coming down on the back.
A real evil place, this.
I gotta get that bottle.
You're free!
Help me!
Kill them!
Ominous bottle.
Bad omen 5.
We gotta find a trial chamber.
I think we have enough raw beef.
Potatoes.
Yeah, it's definitely time to head home, because we are running out of space.
On everything.
They even have a moat around this tower!
Advanced.
What you got for me?
Arrows?
Okay.
String?
Nah!
I don't actually want that.
Arrows.
You know what?
Maybe I say fuck the bone, because I don't have a lot of it.
Yeah.
We don't care about the bone.
Wait, what?
Why did that sound like I just broke my bones?
That was a weird sound.
Also, village up there.
You know what?
I'm gonna follow this river for a bit.
I know it's sort of this way I need to go, but I'm keeping in mind how much I'm going this way.
It's okay.
I know exactly where I am.
There's no way I'm getting lost.
Dude, I feel like there's sort of a lag when I look around on the boat.
Kind of annoying.
I don't know why that's the case.
Yo, this is actually kind of a dope-ass river.
Tell me I'm not gonna get stuck at the end here.
Imagine having, like, bridges across here.
You know, having a whole, I don't know, civilization living here.
Like from the time machine.
With Guy Pearce.
And then I pop out at night, you know?
But that's my thing.
I come out at night from the holes in the ground and I just abduct people.
Women, men, children, everyone who's getting old.
I take them all with me.
Bring them back.
That's a dream.
Dude, this ravine, or whatever this was right here, was actually so epic.
And it terminates in this really nice gulf here.
If that's the right word.
It's beautiful.
Cinema.
Also, I never went to the...
to the ice that I saw in the distance.
But it's okay.
Okay, it's gonna be a long trip home now.
Maybe I'll go swimming a bit since I brought my tank.
You know?
I was gonna find...
Oh, I was gonna find diamonds, right?
Okay, so when we get closer to home, we're gonna find a nice cave.
We're gonna explore it.
And maybe we're gonna do it underwater.
And I'm just gonna have to live with the fact that it's kinda dark.
It'll be okay.
Now, let me see if I remember where I am.
I think I definitely need to go this way a bit.
Could've sworn there would be a torch over there.
Maybe torches don't render at this distance.
And again, I don't really remember this.
Hmm.
Wait, where's the sun?
I am going the right way.
Dude, let's explore this.
Nooo!
There's this over there, so I don't want to.
I'm gonna FaceTime me.
And I'm gonna hate it.
Just thinking about the sound and the awful visuals.
No thanks.
I come back when I'm overpowered.
It's a nice looking island.
That's a nice tree too!
That's like the second nice tree I've seen on this trip.
Look at that.
It's a beaut, Clark!
Wonderful.
Okay, from this angle it's kinda...
It's kinda mid.
I'm gonna delete that screenshot.
I don't want that in my folder.
Okay, a big amount of ocean is correct.
This should be the way.
I'm gonna go slightly off angle here.
Oh god, I really hope I'm not lost.
But I should not be, right?
Cause I'm just going south, pretty much.
There's no way you can get lost here.
I have just gone north.
Oh.
Ayyyy!
That looks familiar!
That has to be the island.
That means we're going this way now.
Wait, that's really big though.
Is that the same island?
I don't know.
Oh, don't do it to me.
Don't do it to me.
What is this?
No!
Don't do it!
Fucking don't do it!
Good.
Woo!
Man.
Dude, isn't this like way bigger than the island I saw?
Coming north?
I feel like this thing is ten times bigger.
Hopefully it is the same island.
But I was on it.
And it didn't feel that big.
So I don't know.
I probably should get ready to sleep.
I'm gonna sleep on this island.
We're gonna sleep among the Danish cows.
It's gonna feel good.
Wait a second.
Is there a cool underwater cave right below this?
Hold the phone.
Dude, it's actually kinda creepy just falling down.
Oh shit, I don't have...
I don't have the tank on.
Yeah, let's not do that.
But the feeling of just zincing is...
Giving me Subnautica vibes, you know?
Kinda scary.
Sleep!
I think we're on the right path!
That looks familiar to me.
Is that a torch?
No.
Don't the yellow flowers look like torches in the distance?
Slightly.
And that's... oh yeah, we're here.
We made it.
I wasn't... I was never doubting.
I know where I was.
I told you.
And let me see what I have here.
We got some experience.
No swamp found though.
Andesites.
Andesite is gonna have to wait until we get a better pickaxe.
I just wanna have looting on it, you know?
Or...
Efficiency.
Before I start on every single andesite.
I could also start blowing things up.
But that requires gunpowder, which I don't have.
Or...
Yo, I just remembered!
We also have the possibility of drilling.
I just haven't quite figured out how to use it effectively yet.
That's what I need to do.
I need to investigate that, actually.
Did I even make a drill?
In this one?
Or was that the last world?
I don't remember.
In any case, I'm gonna make it when I come home.
And I'm gonna grab this as well.
Slowly getting ready for enchantments.
Enchantment!
I'll take that.
Hey!
There's my torch!
Wonderful.
The best part about going home, after having gone north so long, is that it's not lagging anymore.
You know, everything's been loaded in already.
That's a good feeling.
And there's the lone tree.
Also called LT.
That's the name of that tree.
We will never chop down that tree!
BUT!
At one point in the future, I will set fire to it.
It is at an undisclosed date.
There is exactly one trigger in the world that needs to happen before that happens.
And it's actually inevitable.
When I do this one thing, that I will not reveal what is, then I need to set fire to that tree.
In fact, I need to set fire to trees in this general area.
Can you figure out what it is now?
Uh, let me think.
So I will not set fire to this area, but I will set fire to this area.
Huh?
Are you thinking?
Do you see the vision?
There's actually no vision.
I just made that shit up.
There's nothing deep behind it!
I lied!
I'm a liar!
Where's my home?
What over here?
There it is!
We are back home, people!
What a trip.
Unfortunately, no diamonds.
But I didn't really go into a cave, so...
I wouldn't call that a failure.
I would call it standard.
Iron...
Needs to be cooked!
Oh!
Yeah, just cooked that too.
We have gold.
Wait, what is, uh...
Oh, brass sheet and gold, they look similar.
I see.
Also have two smokers now.
Ominous bottle.
That's a random-ass item.
That goes in here.
I think I will relocate my chests inside the house today.
And get a preliminary setup going for item sorting.
Manual item sorting, mind you.
Um...
Give me this.
There.
Oh, this needs to come off.
Come on.
Didn't I have a, uh...
Iron helmet?
Maybe not.
Oh.
Yeah.
Tank.
Honestly, I don't want this helmet.
Or this.
We can make paper.
Ah, but wait, wait, wait!
So, three sugarcane for three paper.
Can we do it better?
No.
Wait.
Book is cardboard.
Three...
Oh, it's just...
Uh, wait a minute.
Book.
Okay, yeah.
It's just cardboard or leather.
I see.
So we're not actually saving paper in any way there.
But I guess, uh...
Nah.
Okay.
Fine.
I'll make paper.
Twenty-seven.
And with that paper, we can make books.
That's not a lot of books, man.
That's...
Whew!
Yeah, we need to find a better way to make books.
For sure.
That was rough.
Only nine books from that whole trip.
That's crazy.
Did get 33 white wool, though.
And, you know what?
We probably need this to make an airplane, right?
So...
Good that we got it.
Apples...
Here.
I wanna grow potatoes!
Some of this becomes potato land now.
Half of it, actually.
I'll fill the rest up with potatoes later.
What else?
Oh, I should've probably done that.
Yeah, this axe is now dead to me.
Oh!
We can delete items!
Yeah!
Sick.
Fire protection.
I'm actually gonna keep these boots.
These boots are sick for the nether.
These are some great nether boots.
Uh...
I'll keep this too for now.
Yep.
Iron.
Cook it!
What else needs to be cooked?
Okay.
Some sand.
We have a lot of sand now.
Six diamonds.
I mean, we can make something out of that, right?
Chest piece or something?
No.
Next?
No!
Boots?
Yes!
But is it worth it?
Yeah.
My boots are about to be destroyed.
Do it.
Cover me with diamonds.
Although, I wouldn't call that covering, but...
Sure.
I have 14 arrows.
That's just not good enough.
I need that bow.
Do I not have any string?
Yeah, I...
Dude, I need to go caving so bad.
To get that diamond.
And...
Wait, wait, wait.
So, to get the diamonds, I gotta go find diamonds.
And the reason I get diamonds is to get diamond armor so I can go caving.
Or just survival in general, I guess.
But I also need to enchant my shit.
Because I'd rather go caving with an enchanted pickaxe.
So to do that, I need books, right?
And I need enchanting table.
Have I done that?
Enchanting table.
I don't think I have!
Let's make it.
Obsidian, diamonds, and book.
Okay.
Fuck.
I don't have any obsidian.
Shit.
Ah!
Oh my god.
I feel like...
Why is progression so hard right now?
I'm usually way better at this.
I feel like I'm being limited by external forces.
It's not me who's doing it.
It's just happening.
Oh wait, we have more sugarcane.
Nether.
Book!
Wait, paper.
And then book.
63, baby!
Yeah!
Okay, okay.
We're actually cooking now.
I think we may be onto something here.
And now, bookcase.
It's just wood!
Easy.
Case.
That's 10!
Not bad!
Now we need to find some obsidian.
Let me actually do a quick...
I'm gonna quickly scan the land.
Bip!
We got lava.
Oh!
Whoa!
That broke fast.
What?
Wasn't that at like 70%?
Fucking useless.
Wow.
Give me that.
Here we go!
Quick sleep.
I'm lost.
No, I'm not.
Wait, there was lava here the entire time?
That's kinda crazy.
I could've sworn there was lava on the other side though, of the lake.
Like, I feel like I remember that.
Weeeeee!
I needed three.
No, four.
Ooh!
I almost went in!
Jesus Christ!
Wow!
One more.
Oi, oi, oi!
I got what I came for.
Oopsie daisy!
Sorry!
I'm gonna snip.
Hey!
I can mill that!
Sick!
Fuck yeah!
I need greenery.
Let me put some greenery here.
And there.
Actually, I'm gonna- no.
It's fine.
Okay.
Time for the thingy.
But we need a book.
We have a book.
Enchantment.
Diamonds.
Good thing I didn't use them all, huh?
There we go!
Okay, so, we gotta be careful now though.
When I plop this down, I can't take it apart easily.
You know?
This is a big decision now.
This is the spot.
Let me think.
I have to remember how this works.
Nope.
Here.
And then we do like...
Yeah.
But!
Hold on.
Hmm.
Maybe I do it over here and- Oh!
Over here instead?
Just because I feel like when I come in, you know, I wanna have...
My chest- No, chests could be over here, I guess.
This is the chest area.
Yeah, that's good.
Chest area over there.
And then here.
We're gonna have- Maybe a little reading corner.
Huh?
A little corner for reading.
Here.
So...
There.
And then...
Right?
I'm confident.
That's it.
Oh, yeah.
It's been a while, my friend.
Bring me what I need.
I need, uh, planks now.
Why only seven?
Not enough planks?
Not enough books, I guess.
Wait, why not?
Oh, I used some for the thingy.
Okay, yeah.
Fine.
Wait, I already had some.
Whoops.
Damn.
I just made too many.
Crap.
Wait, was it even- Yeah, it was, it was.
I was about to say- Wait a minute, was it a chiseled bookshelf?
I don't remember what it is this.
Got the particles.
Alright, alright, alright.
Um...
Here.
Here, here.
And...
I guess I won't be able to see what I need to see anyway.
Because I don't have the levels.
Right?
Where's my blue stuff?
Wait, what?
Did I not collect blue stuff?
I could have sworn I collected blue stuff.
Uh...
No, I definitely collected blue stuff somewhere.
Oh!
There it is.
It was all the way in the beginning.
There we go.
Oh, right, it doesn't stay.
Oh...
Oh my god, oh my god.
Efficiency three is crazy.
That's what we need.
Efficiency and the other thing.
It's not looting, it is...
It is...
Uh...
I forget.
But you know what I mean.
It's out there.
It's the one that gives me...
More.
That's what I want.
I also got some table covers.
Maybe I'll cover this bookshelf in a table.
Wait, what?
Oh, you can...
Interesting.
This seat is reserved for me.
This is the seat cover.
Nobody sits on that except me.
In, in, in.
Give me some...
Calcite?
Where did I even get that?
Meat we have enough of, so we don't need that right now.
Bookshelves we also are doing great on.
Dirt is fine.
That's ascension.
In fact, a little bit more dirt never hurt anyone.
Lapis Lazuli.
Go in here.
Same spot so I don't forget.
Now arrows.
Ah...
Man, I don't have a bow anymore.
I feel like I should wait with arrows until I can make a super good bow with enchanting.
Yeah, that's the plan.
So, check it out.
We're gonna take fire protection now.
No, we're not.
We're not.
Not yet.
I was gonna go into the nether, but that, that, that is later.
We don't need flint and steel.
We don't need this stupid rotten flesh either.
Nobody likes that.
Rest is looking good, man.
We don't need arrows in that case.
I think we're cooking.
Let's go exploring.
Time to go caving.
Now it's all about diamonds.
And this cave we have over here is not that promising with diamonds, but I haven't really explored it fully.
So, who knows.
This is what I mean by not really a diamond biome.
Unfortunately.
This is the biome I'm in now.
Kinda sucks for diamonds.
I could jump down here.
Wait!
No, no, no!
Haha!
I'm not gonna do that, man.
I'm not gonna risk my levels.
No way.
Easy!
I only did that because I knew I was gonna hit it.
Normally I wouldn't, but that one was a sure... deal.
Wait, what?
The frick is that?
Okay, you want a piece of me?
We can dance.
Hey!
Check this out, guys!
Check behind me!
Oh, crap!
Don't fall in the lava!
Lovely experience.
Looks like I was already down here.
Holy crap, that's a lot of...
OH!
I put three here to go up that way.
Oh, is this my own making?
I made that waterfall.
Azarene.
Hmm.
That's a new one.
Diamonds!
So right now, full diamonds, and then we go nether.
Insane gameplay tricks.
Actually so smart.
Ooh, lots of skeletons over there.
Now, diamonds, where are you?
Wait, why is there obsidian here?
Hold on.
What the fuck?
Oh, is it my water I just did?
Maybe I just caused that.
Maybe there was lava here, and I did that.
Just now.
Diamonds.
Kinda want this too.
Also, it's experience, right?
So...
Oh!
Fuck!
Little child.
God, I hate these things.
That guy wants a piece of me.
He's welcome to it!
Call me any time.
Was that your son I just murdered?
Too bad.
See if there's anything up here.
Oh!
Enderman.
We gotta kill him.
It's actually big.
And you know what?
I don't even need a shield, guys.
I mean, I don't need a...
EDP.
E-C money.
I'm EDP free.
Never again we shall EDP.
Except...
In the end.
Oh!
Green guy!
Yes!
You know what that means?
At least what I think it means?
Belts, baby!
Belts!
And suspenders.
And maybe also some glue.
Heyo!
Uh-oh.
There's a lot here!
Yeah!
Oh!
Wait!
No!
I'm not ready.
Come to me.
Oh, they're fighting each other now.
That's good.
What's up, green man?
I'm gonna...
Oh, please drop something for me.
Please.
Don't do this to me.
I need your stuff.
Yeah!
Oh!
I see.
Glue!
That's glue, baby!
We...
I told you, man!
Slime ball!
I can...
I can ponder the slime ball?
Let's see.
Whoa!
A raft!
Disconnected sections of simulated contraptions will split off.
Right?
Is it still simulated?
Looks like it...
Oh, yeah!
Yeah, that looks simulated to me.
A slime ball can be used to merge any two simulated contraptions.
So you put it there.
Does it matter where?
Or...
Dude, how the hell did they code that?
That's nuts.
I see diamonds.
No, wait.
Those are zombies.
Zombies, uh...
Shirts kinda look like diamonds.
Am I crazy?
Like, look at that!
Those little children...
Oh!
Look like diamonds to me.
Thank you.
Yo, wait a minute!
I wonder, though.
If I kill enemies...
With the blaster...
Am I even gonna get experience for it?
I don't think I will.
That's fine, though.
Experience the secondary.
Diamonds.
Very high up, though.
That's why I brought ascension blocks.
I feel so naked without a bow, you know?
You came flying!
That's gonna be me very soon.
I will take to the skies.
Nice.
Uh-oh.
This guy's armored.
Fuck.
Oh, my shield is gone!
Emergency.
We need to make a...
Like an oven.
Frick.
Burn that.
Burn it.
Don't eat these.
Or that.
That's all I need.
Stop!
Maybe I need this, actually.
Nice!
We're back.
This is why you bring wood!
Also gold here.
How much diamonds?
Six diamonds?
It's not that great.
Yeah, see, this place is not what I would call a...
diamond...
biome.
Honestly, this cave is kind of disappointing.
Throw some diamonds.
Nice!
Ooh, there's more.
Level 20?
Oh!
Damn!
What a deposit here.
That's what I needed.
And there's more.
Oh, here they come.
They heard me digging for diamonds.
Oh, no.
Oh my god, these guys are so annoying!
How they always get hidden?
They're fucking...
pieces of shit!
Ah!
I'm dying, I'm dying!
Food me!
Shit!
Oh my god.
Why there's so many children?
We good?
Fuck off.
I'm dead, I'm dead!
Oh, yeah.
Backwards technique.
I'm gonna BTU.
Fuck you.
Oh my god!
So
many all of a sudden!
I'm in light!
I'm gonna die!
No, I'm fine, I'm fine.
Oh my god.
Ah!
Fuck you.
Fuck you!
Boom!
Die, motherfucker!
That's right, you're all dead!
You suck!
You ain't good enough to kill me!
I'm the master!
Nice try, though.
Nearly had me.
Fuck!
Like, what actually happened just now?
I don't understand these mechanics.
Why did that just go crazy like that?
Oh, we got a green guy.
Oh, what the...
Where's that range?
Whatever.
It's like an...
Endless onslaught.
Oh, man.
I am so...
My shoulders are so tense.
Eleven slime balls, baby.
It was all worth it.
And all I wanted was to get that diamond somewhere, and now I don't know where it is.
That diamond?
Oh, hell yeah.
Belongs to me.
Hey.
Stop it.
He baited me.
At the end there.
Oh, more than two!
Yes!
Fifteen diamonds now.
I think I need...
Let me see.
Maybe seven or eight for chest and legs.
So sixteen, let's say, for both.
And then we also need a helmet.
Come on.
A little bit more diamond.
Just a bit.
Oh!
There it was.
That's the one I was trying to get before.
Also, I have no more torches.
Good thing I saw that now.
Where are my...
Hold on.
I didn't bring any coal.
Uh...
Well...
Crap.
This is not good.
Let this be like five diamonds.
There's four diamonds hidden behind this one.
You'll see.
One.
Two.
Three!
Four!
What'd I say?
And now we need just a little bit...
One more.
Just a couple more.
Oh, I don't have any torches.
Uh...
Maybe I'm done here.
Oh!
Diamond!
I'm not done.
You behind me?
Someone was behind me.
Yeah, definitely we have enough now.
I'm leaving.
I'm out of here!
Gonna get a little bit of gold on the way out.
The victory lap.
Go!
Now, where is my exit?
Uh...
I think it was over here.
No.
Was it?
There should be arrows around the water.
Ah, but wait, that's further up, I think.
Because I jumped down...
Oh, I jumped from here.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's what I did.
So...
We're gonna take this water.
Now I'm ready for the nether.
Obviously, we still gotta wear some gold.
It's kinda precarious having lava right there.
Oh, we're going real far up.
Oh!
I'm drowning!
Alright, we're good.
I thought someone was attacking me.
Ah!
Good enough.
Decent.
I can find my way home from here.
Oh, no!
Whoops.
We gotta fix that.
Okay, so where's home?
This way.
Yeah, there's the lake.
It's over here.
Has to be.
Wait, no.
Torch over there.
The mountain is there, so it has to be here.
Torch?
Yeah, it is here.
Okay, so I thought I was going crazy, but no.
I was totally not crazy.
I found it.
Alright, full armor now.
It finally happened.
Legs.
Chest.
And...
Boots.
No, wait, wait.
I have those already.
Oh, yeah, I had those already.
Great.
Oh, I want to make helmet.
Helmet because I have the crazy boots.
I have the nether boots.
These ones with fire protection.
And let's not forget I have fire protection potions too!
Oh, I'm so ready.
I was born ready for this.
Um...
You go in here.
No, you can cook a little bit.
Teedling.
Diamonds.
Feel good in my tummy.
All this armor we don't actually need now.
Oh, hold on.
Slime ball.
We got new stuff!
Should I make a slime block?
Oh, that's a lot of slime for that though.
I don't think I should do it.
Let me see what else I can make.
Lead!
Ah, that's how you make that.
I see.
Package frog port.
Wait, I can make leather?
Oh, right.
Of course.
Super glue.
We need to make this.
Iron sheet and nuggets.
Alright.
I'm just gonna quickly do this for a bit.
And then we're gonna go to the nether.
Ooh, let's ponder on that.
Super glue groups blocks together into moving contraptions.
Yeah.
Tell me more.
Clicking two endpoints creates a new glued area.
Yeah.
But they were already connected in this animation.
Remove a box.
Punch it with the glue item in hand.
Okay.
I see.
Adjacent blocks sharing an area will pull each other along.
Sharing an area.
Okay.
Wait a fucking second.
Are you saying...
That I can...
Hoist my entire house up?
And relocate it?
Is that what they're fucking saying?
Wait a fucking minute.
This is insane.
Whoa.
Overlapping glue volumes will move together.
Okay.
I just ha- I just got some grand ideas in my head.
Dude!
I'm gonna steal a mansion!
We're totally stealing a mansion.
I will steal it.
I will bring that back home and turn it into a factory!
I don't even pay attention anymore.
Whatever.
I'm happy with that.
Okay, let me see what else.
Show me the good stuff.
Black hot air envelope?
Okay.
Sticky piston?
That makes sense.
Wait, that was it?
Not to be that guy, but...
That's it?
No more?
Oh, sticker!
What the hell is this?
Stone alloy.
What the hell is that?
Stickers are ideal for redstone controlled block attachment.
Oh, so powered, it's sticking like an electromagnet?
That's what I'm guessing here.
Upon receiving a signal, it will toggle its state.
Yes, more.
If it is now moved in a contraption, the block will move with it.
Yes.
This is still a little bit abstract for me, but with the whole, you know, moving blocks around.
Toggled once again, the block is no longer attached.
So that if this starts spinning, it's gonna stay.
Okay.
Very cool.
This superglue is my one and only now.
We put that here.
Wonderful.
Discoveries are being made.
It's a good feeling.
Oh shit, we have no room now.
We need a separate box here.
And you know what?
Let's start making those boxes in the other room.
That's right.
I've had it.
No more outside.
Uh, box.
No, chest.
Chest.
Two of them.
This area over here is going to be my...
My area.
This will be...
Um...
Ah...
I don't wanna do that now, man.
Ah, I really should do it now, but I don't want to.
Maybe... Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Maybe there's a way to pick up this chest with all the contents?
Let's...
Plop it down inside.
That's gotta be a way.
Maybe like a little suction cup or something.
There's gotta be a way to do that later.
I believe.
Maybe I can manually crank it, you know?
I crank the suction cup.
Sounds amazing.
Ah, my...
Ah!
I hate this chest!
Ew.
I need to... I need to fix something here.
Okay.
What the fuck ever, dude.
I'm bringing all the weird stuff that we made from Create in here.
Right now.
And then we take all the stuff out that's not that.
Which means...
This, that...
This...
This goes in the other box, yeah.
Cardboard, honestly, that's...
Also not quite okay.
Alright.
Oh!
There was...
There was more.
In.
I just don't wanna have this chest be filled anymore.
I'm losing my mind.
What the hell was this thing?
Brass hand.
In.
Good.
Much better.
We good?
I think we're good.
Oh!
I'm so much more calm now after that.
Whew!
That's what I needed.
Look how clean this is now.
Oh, man.
That does wonders for your sanity.
It really does.
Cardboard, let's put that in here.
Oh, this chest is also starting to get on my nerves now.
Do I leave it?
I'm gonna leave it.
Don't eat this.
Boat, we definitely need to keep.
I guess redstone dust is kind of something that belongs in here.
Maybe there's new potions.
Who knows?
Uh, I do need a bow.
Oh, man.
I need one more string, I think.
Oh, we can make string!
We can make string.
Uh, wait.
How does that work?
String.
Mill!
Let's mill that shit.
Yeah, wha-
There we go.
Three string.
Then we need some sticks as well, if I'm not mistaken.
What do I need?
This one.
Nice!
And now, the arrows.
Fourteen.
Eighteen is not too bad.
It's just for emergencies in there, you know.
Otherwise, I'm gonna go in melee.
Now that I have diamond.
Okay, I think we're good!
Ready to go.
Oh, potions!
Fire protection!
That's very much needed.
I got three of them.
Yep.
And I think that's pretty much it for this part.
Thirty sticks.
I'll take some sticks with me.
No!
I'll take some wood with me.
Just a bit.
Toolbox, of course.
Spike glass.
Torches!
We need torches.
Wait, where's all my coal?
There it is.
I was almost losing my mind.
They brought home so much.
Let's do one stack.
There.
Thank you.
And then...
In with the coal.
And out with that.
Yes!
Let's go!
Arrow ready.
Axe.
Shield is good.
Let's do it.
Bed is also there.
In fact, I'm gonna sleep right here.
There.
Let's go.
Objective.
Experience.
Experience and...
Well, pretty much just experience.
That's the main thing.
Maybe this actually to make more arrows.
Yeah, let's do that first.
Oh, I hear ghosts everywhere.
Please don't hurt me.
I can hear when they shoot.
I'm ready.
Did some of them fall down?
I hope not.
Ah, here we go.
Man, look at this guy.
Shooting and then hiding again.
I wonder...
Wait a second.
What if I come in here with cardboard?
Can I be stealthy?
Will they even know I'm here?
I need to experiment with that.
In fact, I need to experiment with cardboard in general.
Oh, shit.
Wow, you're sneaky!
Look at him!
Shooting and then going up again.
Back to sender.
No!
Bastard.
Okay.
Let's make those arrows, shall we?
How does that even work?
Oh my god.
Arrow.
Oh no.
Do I need a table for that?
Piss.
I hate the table.
Fine.
30 arrows!
Now we're cooking.
Crip the food.
Let's get some experience.
And we cannot get lost, obviously.
This is bad.
I don't think I want to go that way.
Looks like a bad path.
Down is also kind of questionable.
I see some experience here.
And it's also a bad path.
Maybe I simply go up or something.
I mean, I see some there and there and there.
Actually, there's everywhere.
And we gotta kill endermen.
Oh, I was fast on that one.
Fastest gun in the west.
Dead end.
I'll use dirt.
You know what I could do?
I could also go to the fortress, now that I have fire protection.
And form the blazes.
Experience, and we get the rods.
Which is actually great fuel for a furnace.
I'm just gonna grab this real quick.
I think that's a good idea.
Use the potion to its fullest, you know?
And who knows?
I haven't really tried to see how much experience it is.
Okay.
I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna get over there.
I'm gonna systematically take out these fuckers.
The fuckers who are very hot.
We're not gonna be distracted by their hotness.
We're gonna simply kill them.
We're gonna end their life.
Steal their life force.
Ow.
Actually, drink the potion now.
Quick!
There we go.
So I think that was a spawn thingy...
there-ish.
You can't hurt me now!
What's up, friends?
Let me see the experience.
Oh, it's a good amount of experience.
I like...
Oh!
Uh-oh.
These guys are still scary, though.
I'm not immune to those.
That's one limitation.
Oh, there's a lot of skeletons over there.
Where are these guys spawning at?
I need to find that spot.
Are they over here?
Is that it?
Here it is!
This is it.
Now we just chill.
Maybe I actually go kill this guy.
Oh!
Oh my god, they're here!
I can't burn!
I'm immune to burning.
Sweet.
Hey, wait!
Where did this guy come from?
Do they also spawn here?
I don't mind, though.
That's more fire protection.
We got cream!
Yeah!
Keep spawning!
Experience me!
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
I need to calm down a little bit.
I'm getting overexcited.
This is what peak gameplay looks like.
Experience.
Materials.
Satisfaction.
Yeah.
I wish they would spawn faster, though.
It's a little too slow for me.
Come on!
Maybe I walk away.
Is that the trick?
I walk away and come back?
No?
Yo!
I was about to say, let's put in a blaster here and just kill them.
But I don't think they're gonna die from blasting these guys.
Of all the guys, these are probably not the ones.
Maybe we can do like a drill or something.
I don't know if that damages enemies.
Oh, that's a good chunk here.
That's a good chunk.
I don't want you to fall that way.
I need experience.
I don't know if it's that fast.
Maybe it's faster to mine.
Oh!
Oh no!
It's over!
I gotta go, I gotta go, I gotta go!
Wow!
Where did they come from?
Holy crap!
Woo!
That was scary.
I managed.
No problem.
Maybe I should have a sword against these guys, you know?
Feel that AoE.
Oh!
Oh no!
Oh, it's still scary.
It's still scary.
I got him though.
I can definitely feel the difference with the diamond armor.
Last time these skeletons hit me, I almost died instantly.
I think I heard another one.
Six blaze rods!
Not bad, huh?
How long do I have left?
Three minutes.
One normal hit, one crit.
Then you kill them.
Are you up there?
You're up there, I see you.
Oh!
This is a pretty good experience actually!
Almost 28 now?
Yeah, I think I have to walk away from this and then they spawn.
Alright, at least it increases chances.
Now I walk this way.
Oh, maybe not actually.
Maybe they just spawn.
And it's random.
I'm gonna explore a little bit.
Hey, I know you're there.
Haha!
Good job!
Oh, we got another spawner here!
Great!
Bro.
There we go.
Dude, I can alternate between this and the other.
I run back and forth.
It is a little far away though.
But maybe it's worth...
If I go here now?
Wait, am I even going the same way?
No, I'm not.
Wait, where the hell am I?
Hey!
We can turn that into a saddle?
Not bad.
Okay.
Finally, the saddles are useful!
Wait, what the...
Where am I going?
Wait...
What the...
That's the same portal.
That's crazy!
Wow!
There's no way!
This is that portal I went into when I went north!
Wow.
I just don't remember where I came from here.
This way, I think.
What's this over here?
Oh, that's where I was.
Right.
Please spawn!
Come on!
Spawn for me.
Oh wait, I don't have fire protection.
Glittering!
Nice.
Almost 29?
The first enchant is coming in hot soon!
Spawn for me.
How are you not dead yet?
Man, they're being stingy with these guys right now.
Come on!
Usually they're everywhere.
Here he comes.
Okay, I'll kill you too.
Why not?
You know what?
Maybe we should make a shortcut from here to the spawner.
Oh wait, I hear skeletons.
Hey!
Uh oh!
It's you.
It's you, you bastard.
Oh, now they're over there.
Yeah, they kind of spawn where you are not, you know?
Which does make sense.
Uh oh, the archer and the black guy there is not good.
That's a bad combo.
There we go.
Come here.
Come on.
Shit.
Nice.
Handle that.
How's my shield doing?
Oh!
It's almost too...
Oh, it's almost about to collapse.
You think I checked, huh?
Oh, that's a lot of place.
Gimme, gimme, gimme.
Ho-ho-ee!
Very nice.
Four minutes on that.
Shield is holding up a little.
We can go for a little longer.
30!
Maybe go a little further.
Just at least until the potion is worn off, you know?
I see you down there.
I'm actually getting coal.
Killing these guys.
These guys are not that bad anymore.
I feel like I'm pretty proficient at murdering them.
And I'm getting materials.
This is actually the best part, you know?
I kill these, I get experience, I get the cream.
It's wonderful.
Jump at me.
I need you to come over here.
Please don't stand there.
Oh, that's it, that's it.
That's more like it.
Yeah, okay, okay!
Uh-oh.
I'm kinda stuck in a little bit of a corner here.
But it's fine.
I wonder if I can capture these guys, take them with me.
Nice.
Got a lot of cream out of that.
Okay, you know what actually?
This is actually so much more experience.
I'm just looking at my experience bar right now, and it's flying.
When I grab that.
Compared to killing these guys here.
But, you know.
Killing these guys nets me stuff like...
The blaze stuff, you know?
So, it's nice.
Oh, look at that.
Oh no, he disappeared.
How many juicy tar...
Were there just cream people flying from the sky just now?
That looked weird.
Look at this train.
Actually professional.
Don't even get hit once.
Oh, I'm so good.
That was magnificent.
Now we ascend.
In fact, slowly and surely, we're gonna make a staircase here.
At some point, the staircase will be complete.
But it is not today.
Okay, so I definitely need to get to 33.
Minimum.
Not the most efficient ascension, but...
It works.
I need to make a path for myself.
So I can get access to stuff like this down here.
Pretty easily.
Because that's where the experience is.
Ho!
Come on!
Ah!
I was trying to hit them with the fire.
I need to flex on them.
Here we go.
32.
Okay.
You guys think I'm gonna get lucky with my two enchants that I have?
I need efficiency.
And then I need...
The other thing.
What is the other thing?
The one that gives me more.
Honestly, maybe I want efficiency.
More than the other thing.
Man, I don't like this spot here!
We're gonna find a new spot.
Soon.
It's like a little island here.
I'm stranded.
Are you stuck down there?
What a shot.
I'm at the point where I don't need this material.
I just want experience.
Almost there.
And what about bastions, man?
Can I get some of that?
I'm ready.
Fight me, bro.
Dude, where's all the experience?
There's nothing up here.
Dude, what the...
Horrible place in the nether here!
And I'm gonna get lost.
That should be it.
There it is!
33!
We got two enchants coming up.
They need to be good.
I believe.
I'm pretty sure the current enchant for the axe is efficiency 3.
Which is, you know...
Not great.
I would like efficiency 5.
Let me loot your tears.
There's also tears back there!
I'm taking that.
And where the hell are the endermen?
I feel like there's usually a bunch of endermen in the nether.
And yet...
Haven't seen a single one.
I'm outta here.
The moment of truth!
Come on!
Pickaxe.
You ready?
Oh wait, I don't have the blue stuff.
I mean, it's not bad.
I think I'll take it.
FORTUNE!
That's the one I needed!
I think.
Efficiency 3.
Hold on, I'm gonna try another pickaxe.
Oh wait, do I even have...
Awww.
I have no more diamonds.
Shit.
Crap.
And I can't enchant it again, right?
Well, I guess I could disenchant it.
That's rough.
Why is it not efficiency 4?
I guess I can do efficiency 3 on my axe.
Ah, but I should...
I should really...
Enchant something now.
Right?
Otherwise it's wasted.
Maybe I'll do these boots.
Or this one.
Or my axe.
I could just do my axe, I guess.
Also, wait a minute.
Do I even have enough bookshelves?
I forgot the exact number I needed.
No.
Fuck.
Honestly, I'm just gonna...
Do that.
I used all my bookshelves.
I'm torn between axe or...
Ooh, fire protection.
That's not bad, actually.
Protection is better, though.
This is more universal.
I feel like fire protection...
I don't really need that, because I have potions for that.
You know what I mean?
So, I'd rather just take this.
But...
Yeah.
Section three.
Then we're gonna go get some more diamonds, so we can enchant another pickaxe.
This is already a great step up, though.
So the mission now is, we're gonna go get diamonds, and and decide at the same time.
Because now that we have efficiency, it's gonna go a lot faster.
This is the plan.
And it's a good one.
Exotic items in here.
Um...
Fuck this.
Saddle, we can churn, right?
Churn that shit.
Who needs a saddle, not me.
Use of glowstone dust, so we can make more arrows if we need to.
When it's time.
Don't need that one.
Blaze rod, so check it out!
Wait, how did this work again?
Why isn't that, uh...
Because that doesn't burn?
Ah, there we go.
Okay, nice.
Leave one there.
Here.
Actually, one more.
One more too.
Charcoal!
Oh yeah, this was making charcoal.
Let's just keep doing that.
That's good.
Very nice.
Put this back on.
Put this on now.
Ah, but wait, these were good for nether.
But I'm not going to the nether now.
So it's actually good.
Still keep some wood.
Don't need this right now, either.
Who needs this crap?
Moss carpet?
Burn that.
Okay, what do I need to burn?
Honestly, the rest is good.
I like the rest.
Shield, shield, shield, shield, shield.
Before anything.
And then we burn the other.
We are so ready for combat here.
Look at this.
Protection three and diamond.
Ooh, yeah.
Wonderful.
It's exotic.
Keep these.
Oh, I should have tried enchanting the bow!
Wait, maybe I can still try.
Hey!
Wait a minute.
That's actually sick.
I should do that!
I'm actually doing it.
Holy crap.
I have arrow problems right now.
Oh!
30!
Okay.
That's fine.
I'll be...
I'll be 30 soon.
In fact, I need to go get some diamonds real quick and then...
We're going back to the nether.
We have all of this...
I don't want to go in the same cave, actually.
Or maybe I do and I go in a different direction down there.
Yeah, that's good.
We go towards the dark spots.
Oh, man.
That is just...
Makes the heart pump.
Okay, you know what?
That's too rich for me.
Good night!
Kill him.
God, I fucking hate these skeletons!
They drive me crazy.
I feel like their cadence is too high, you know?
Oh, I feel the difference in the mining speed!
Oh, it feels incredible.
And look at all this.
Oh, yeah.
So much better.
But not good enough.
We need more.
Oh, we also need zinc.
I'll grab some of that too.
Yo, I should make a pyramid.
Make a pyramid near a huge andesite deposit.
And we go to town.
Oh, I forgot about the drilling situation.
We need to explore that.
I need to figure that out.
Next time I'm home.
I'm gonna think about it.
Ah!
Give me a moment's rest, please!
What is this, Terraria?
I'm not seeing any diamonds.
I gotta be honest.
Man, I hate this cave, actually.
The more I think about it, the more I hate it.
Just because of the lack of diamonds.
Oh, I heard you.
Yeah, please explode.
Be my guest.
What about here?
Wait, I feel like I've been here.
I was here before.
Like in that exact spot.
Let's go this way.
Looks promising.
Enderman!
Oi, oi, oi, oi, oi, oi, oi!
Come to me.
Oh, you're shooting each other!
That's great.
Love it.
Where are these diamonds at?
Oh, look at that one!
There's a mine here!
That means diamonds.
I'm going up there.
I guess we just go straight.
Wait, is there lava?
There's lava there.
Maybe get ready with some...
deep slate.
Aha!
I see.
Nope.
Not on my watch.
There we go!
What did I say?
Only one though.
Hmm.
I feel like I should be collecting these.
Apparently trains.
You know?
Ah, zinc!
Oh,
man.
I feel...
Why is it, like, pulling teeth?
To get these diamonds right now.
I mean, I'll take some more.
Diamonds!
Yes, sir!
Come on, please be more than one.
Ah!
Ooh, that was actually kind of close.
Getting a little complicated, the layout here.
Okay, maybe it's just a theory, but...
I feel like when you're in the mines like this, you can't find more than one diamond at a time, or at least it's much rarer.
Down here, there's only, like, one.
At a time.
I'm just gonna dig.
I've got that digging feeling.
I'm just gonna go wherever the dig takes me.
Would you look at that!
The dig led me to pleasure.
Mm-mm.
Except there's no chests here.
Kinda hoping for that.
Let's pull out this bad boy.
Fill them up with some good stuff.
All kinds of ores, actually.
This is the ore box.
Now.
Checking that I have it.
As soon as we're out of the mines, we get multiple diamonds.
Hashtag confirmed.
Theory correct.
No, no!
We're gonna keep digging.
Further down, this is the rule.
Just go!
Believe.
Believe in me.
I don't actually need more of that.
Oh!
We have reached the very bottom.
What a bummer.
We cannot go deeper right now.
Maybe this direction.
I hear lava.
That's a good sign of diamonds as well.
We got a zinc here.
Don't mind if I take that.
In fact, I think I need more zinc than I need andesite in the long run.
The bottleneck is me applying that stuff every time.
Oh, shit.
I ran out of stuff here.
Oh, no!
I don't have any coal!
Oh, shit!
Whatever.
We're going in dark.
No torches.
You think I'm afraid?
I have diamond armor.
I can't die.
How many diamonds did I find?
Only two diamonds?!
No, wait, wait.
That can't be right.
Oh, thank god.
Man, I nearly had a heart attack.
I keep wanting to pull down torches, but I can't.
We're going in dark.
Hey, dude.
I'm not afraid.
Are you afraid?
Something is following me.
Where the hell are they?
I can hear you.
Oh, there's a chest right there.
Turn off the light.
Okay, well, we got some of these.
Darkness gaming.
Fine, okay.
Honestly, we have the diamonds we need.
Let's get out of here.
I'm happy.
We got what we came for.
See ya!
Straight up.
It is going to be night outside.
I have it on good authority this time.
Inside information.
Straight up, straight up.
Ooh, is that what I think it is?
No way.
Hey!
Would you look at this.
Thank you.
I keep that, actually.
Hmm.
Oh.
That was a bad one.
That's a good one.
Nope.
That was not grown either.
Shit.
Bang, bang.
What a feeling.
Ah, ah, bah, bah, bah!
Dancing queen.
Hate when she dances.
Here we go.
You ready?
It's night.
It's coming.
It's almost here.
We're not quite there yet.
Come on, game!
It's taking a while.
How far down am I?
We need the night now.
It's going to turn day before we know it.
And then I'm going to be wrong again.
I've yet to be right one time.
Cool!
Okay, we can't take it.
Faster.
Fuck is that?
Sounds like a UFO or something.
We got aliens down here.
Here we go!
Night, night, night, night, night, night, night!
Yeah!
What did I say?
Fuck, I'm so good at predictions.
But where am I?
I have no clue where I am.
I gotta get up and look.
This ain't familiar, bruh.
Also, we need to be level 30.
Wait, what the f...
Where the hell am I?
Look at this!
That looks so cool!
What a little village down there!
Oh!
Tried to get me out on the edge there, you little bastard!
Trying to corner me.
That's not gonna happen today.
Okay, so obviously this is not the way home.
How far could we possibly have gone?
Wait a second, is this that spot?
This is not the spot with the bees, is it?
Can't be.
Let me go to bed, I need to see where I am.
Shit!
Sleep!
Quick, quick, quick!
Aw, you...
Fucking asshole!
Preventing my sleep.
We got something new.
Get rid of that.
Where's the sun?
Aha!
Actually, it doesn't help me.
Because I don't know where I am.
But there's no aha.
Let's just go this way.
Let's see what's down here.
Wait, why is there diorite here?
No!
I went back!
Okay, this way now.
How did I go in the exact same direction that I came from?
Leave me alone.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Dude, where on earth are we right now?
I can't have gone that far in the cave, can I?
I don't even remember any of these mushrooms.
This is all foreign to me.
Oh, oh, wait, wait, wait.
No.
Wow, I must have gone far.
Whoa.
How am I so lost?
There's a beach here.
That's not the right one.
Oh, tell...
Yeah, I think I know where I am.
Yeah!
It could only have been here, you know?
I was like, I'm on this mountain that is usually to my left.
And I was.
Good.
Okay, we gotta get a...
Oh, we're going to the nether real quick.
We have a quick nether exploration to do.
Just a quickie.
I'm gonna leave some of this stuff here.
No, not that one.
I'm going this way.
Here's this.
Buffer, yo!
No, I don't like this way.
Ow!
Wait, am I...
Oh, I'm not wearing gold!
Sorry!
Sorry, I'll be back.
With your precious metal on my skin.
Oh, I picked it all up again.
God, the fucking delete button.
Where are you?
Okay, gold time.
Here, let's actually cook this.
There we go.
In...
Ah, there's no room!
Whatever.
Go!
I feel good.
Take me to 30.
I forgot what the next enchantment is that I need.
I'm just gonna go to 30 though, no more.
Because I don't think my mental can handle it.
There's gotta be some in the ceiling.
Yeah, I see some.
We have some here.
Hopefully more than just one.
Oh!
Oh!!
We're good!
Whoo!
I panicked, I panicked a little bit there.
Man.
30!
I made it.
Okay, and now we can make a pickaxe and we can get a fresh enchant.
And it's gonna be a good one.
Wait, where's my...
Let's see!
Wait.
We got it.
Oh, I also... Oh, wait a minute.
This is... Oh, this is what I wanted to do, actually.
Oh.
Aww.
Just infinity, but that's okay.
It's fine.
Let me see what I can do here.
Efficiency 2.
SILK TOUCH!
Guys, we gotta get to 30.
I'll be back.
We gotta go back to the nether.
We need silk touch.
Fuck!
Let's find a really good spot now and get a lot of experience.
Because I've had it with these mediocre spots.
Let's actually just drop down to something promising.
Right here.
Wait, I have no torches.
Ah...
I can't.
I can't do it.
Ah, you know what?
It's fine.
Did I just hit a pig and explode on them?
In fact, I'll probably just go somewhere else, make a portal, and enter the nether from some other place.
In fact, I like that.
I like it a lot.
Now I just want to build things.
Because I've got a bunch of new things that I just want to try.
Exotic.
Amethysts, and...
I guess we don't need arrows anymore, technically.
Oh, man, I...
Okay, we're gonna fill this up, too.
This is now also equipment.
I don't like it, but it is what it is.
In fact, let's take all this and put that in here instead.
Ah, this shield sucks.
Burn it.
Nah.
Here.
Exotic.
Okay, let's see.
What did I get?
There's definitely something I want to make here.
I could try to make that.
Oh, the drill!
Did we already make it?
I think it's in here.
If anything, it's got to be in here.
Nope.
It ain't.
Propeller.
Propeller bearing?
I think I made that one.
Didn't make this one yet.
Hey, I can make these goggles.
String, golden sheets, and that.
Tell me I have glass.
Ah, but I do have sand.
So let's cook some.
Wait, that doesn't work.
That's gonna cook.
Okay, we got zinc ingots.
Let's turn these into these.
And then grab some andesides.
I think that's actually in my box.
Yeah!
Nice.
In fact, give me half of this.
Get ready to cook.
Alloys, baby!
54!
Yes!
Very good.
We're also gonna cook that.
We also have more here.
We actually have more, so we can do this now.
Uh, Andesites.
There we go.
That's cooking nicely.
Do we have food that needs cooking?
A little bit.
Glass, and then I needed the gold sheet.
Goggles needed string.
I have it.
Nice!
Look at that!
Kitted out!
Let's see.
Oh, I jumped a couple things here.
Equip engineer's goggles and a wrench.
Drive-by exchange...
Let me see here.
Superglue some blocks into a group.
Create a contraption with drills.
Saw's or harvesters on board.
That's exactly what I want to do!
That's exactly what I want to do.
Okay.
Use a mechanical press and a basin to create fewer items from more.
Mechanical press and a basin.
Right.
I see.
I think I want to start with this.
Because this is the natural thing I want to do with the drill.
What does the drill take?
One casing, iron, and three ended.
Okay.
Wait, what?
One casing.
I have it.
What the hell did I...
Did I put it over here?
I think I did.
What else do I need to bring?
Superglue?
And...
Maybe I'll take...
Nah.
Leave it.
I think that's good.
Maybe that one.
Yep.
Let me see here.
Drill.
Ironing it.
There we go, baby!
Let me see the...
I gotta look at this again.
Yes, so it breaks it.
Got it.
Depends on the rotational input.
Here we go.
This is what I'm looking for, man.
Whenever drills are moved as part of an animated contraption.
But how do I make it just...
Go!
Like, and not just...
Ten blocks.
I want it to go, like...
A hundred thousand blocks!
It will break blocks.
The contraption runs them into.
Yeah.
Okay, I get that.
I get that.
Inventories attached to the contraption will pick up their drops automatically.
Yes.
I guess I could just keep adding wood to this, make this longer.
Or maybe I can use a minecart.
But how would that work with the...
I would have to put down some rails.
So wait.
I make a one by two tunnel first.
Minecart on it.
And then I somehow attach this.
With glue?
Or what?
I don't know if you see my vision here.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Imagine we move one direction like this.
But at the same time we also move like this.
So together it's this.
Huh?
You see what I'm saying?
Or maybe we go bzzzt, bzzzt, bzzzt, bzzzt, bzzzt, and then bzzzt, you know, and then up, you know, and then together.
Make sense?
Nice.
Well, we got the glue.
I probably need to make more, right?
Like how long...
Is it...
Oh!
Is it just one glue?
For one block?
Hey.
I can't hit!
Fuck you.
That was the worst aim of all time.
I saw a bee.
No, it was a rotating thing.
Looked like a bee.
Wait, what is the point of these actually?
Augments hot with miscellaneous information...
Miscellaneous information about placed components.
Kinetic components show added stress impact or capacity...
Right.
Stressometer, blah, blah, blah.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Item and fluid...
Okay!
Let me actually see that then.
Fluid content, you say.
A thousand millibar?
That doesn't make sense.
Milli...
Uh...
I don't...
I don't know.
Millie Botions.
Millie...
Brim...
Brass...
Bazinga.
I don't know.
Jackie!
It's not eating time yet.
Okay.
I think at this point she's just enjoying getting picked up and put on the floor again.
That's why she keeps jumping up, you know?
Anyway, this is done cooking.
So we put in some zinc.
No, put in this first.
All right.
Let's see what else I can make real quick.
Before I start that experiment.
Fluid valve.
Mixer.
What was this one?
Rose quartz.
I made it, didn't I?
I made this.
I have it somewhere.
But there was no...
There was nothing I could do with it.
Not yet, at least.
Attribute filter.
Crafter slot cover.
Okay.
You want to be up here, Jackie?
You can be up here.
But you gotta sit...
Like...
Can you stay like that?
I have Jackie on my lap now.
Never mind, she wants...
Why do you want to jump up then if you don't want to be here?
Huh?
No.
Don't walk into the microphone.
Jackie.
Don't do it.
I lost my train of thought.
This one.
I want to try and make that.
But I think I have it already, actually.
Let's not make it.
Yeah.
Also, maybe there's some categories.
Maybe this is easier to explore.
My...
Wait a minute.
My card coupling?
Wait a second.
Alloy sheet.
Looks like a telephone.
Okay, we...
We gotta try this, actually.
So, basically, what I think this is...
You plop down some...
Jackie!
No!
Off with you.
You jack...
You, uh...
You jack down...
You jacky down...
You know what I mean.
Wait, what the hell was that just now?
Wheat seeds.
Weightless.
That's what the...
That's what the goggles do!
They give me extra stuff on the items I hover.
Ah,
okay.
That's good to know, actually.
Let's just keep these goggles on and see what else changes.
I was gonna put down some minecarts.
That was the whole plan.
So, give me this.
Let's make a little contraption here.
Like that, right?
We're gonna have a block at each end, just so we don't run off to infinity.
Let's do...
This.
I mean, the thing I was thinking of is coupling two minecarts.
I don't know what that animation was just now.
No!
Don't make another.
Dumbass.
We need minecarts!
So, ironing it's minecart.
Ah!
Ah, but wait a second then.
Wait a second.
Hold on.
If I put it closer...
Is it gonna stay that distance?
So, that's exactly what I expected then.
That is exactly what I expected from this.
Oh, wait.
They get pulled together.
Sweet.
But now my question is, what if I were to do...
Can I somehow attach this?
Whoops.
To the minecart.
Zero SU at current speed.
Spin units?
Maybe?
No?
Okay, wait.
Is it superglue?
Stop getting in the cart!
Wait a minute.
Maybe it actually says something about it.
Summary.
Chains to gather individual minecarts, causing them to move as a group.
Yes, okay.
Right.
Hold on.
What else do I have about mines?
Minecart...
I need minecart with drill.
Or even better, minecart with block, so I can attach drills to the block, you know?
Hmm.
Okay.
I mean, maybe I can just use the rod, like they do in the animation.
But I guess I would have to use...
Oh, what item is that?
It was like some kind of...
It's some kind of item you can just add on to.
Which one is that?
Actually, give me this one too.
Rope coupling.
Oh, that was for the...
Yeah, okay.
Shaft, I think we definitely need, but let's not take it yet.
Actually put this back as well.
Let me have another look through the book.
There's got to be some more stuff with this.
Let's see.
White post box.
Look, super heavy.
Wait, what does that matter?
Is that for like aircraft and stuff?
Like if I make an aircraft out of this, it's gonna be, you know, less likely to fly.
That's what I imagine.
Sandpaper.
Let's make that.
Paper, sand.
That makes sense.
Sandpaper.
Hell yeah, let's make that one.
Paper.
Oh wait, do I even have paper?
I can make paper.
I have this realization every time.
Wait, I may even have something in there now.
Oh, leather.
Right.
No, wait a minute.
This is...
No, wait.
This makes string.
But string makes paper!
Right?
I swear to God it does.
It does make paper.
Okay, you know what?
I wanna try this.
This is like the next step.
I'm gonna get a little bit of...
Sugar.
Show me the sugar.
What's up, dude?
You know where there's sugar?
Man, I harvested all the sugar, didn't I?
Dude, I need one sugar cane!
Oh!
I see it.
I'm coming!
We're gonna make that paper.
We're gonna use that sand.
We're gonna make sandpaper.
And then I'm gonna...
How much you wanna bet it's just to make basalt smooth or some bullshit?
I don't wanna smooth my basalt.
I like my basalt rough!
Kinda like that I have some lava at my disposal whenever I need it.
For example, if I want to make a blaster.
Paper!
Sandpaper!
Now, sand.
We got it.
Sand.
Sandpaper!
Ooh!
New recipes unlocked!
Is it in here?
Ah!
Oh!
Sandpaper polishing.
Okay!
Oh, shit!
Wait, how did I make this?
I turned it into this, I think!
Uh-oh.
How did I...
How did I get that, actually?
Hold on.
Quartz.
Oh!
Nether quartz.
Red.
I have that!
Hey!
No problem!
God, my inventory sucks.
Let's put this, uh...
Minecart coupling in there.
Same with that one.
Noooo!
Keep that one.
Put a saw in there.
Okay.
Now.
Quartz.
So, how do I sandpaper this?
Do I put it down?
Wait, uh...
Let me see.
Can be used to refine materials.
The process can be automated with a deployer.
Okay.
Applies polish to items held in the offhand or lying on the floor when looking at them.
For some reason, I...
The way I pictured that was me on the floor on my back.
You know, you have to lie down and then wrap the thing together.
That sounded so dumb.
Let's put that there.
Uh...
Here.
Yeah!
Look at me wrap that!
Supercharged!
Let me see that achievement.
Which one is that?
Supercharged.
Whoa!
I just jumped the tech tree.
Polish some rose quartz.
Place and power a deployer.
The perfect reflection of yourself.
AI!
Fuck yeah, dude.
I like it.
Uh...
Okay.
So, what is new?
Blink for me.
Something just happened, right?
Oh!
Electron tube!
Rose quartz lamp!
Interesting.
Wait.
I gotta clean up first.
Can't be messy like this.
There we go.
I'm gonna put the ingots in here.
The string is weightless?
That's not true.
That's a lie.
String does weigh something.
Um...
Electron tube.
I'm gonna put the ingots in here.
Iron sh...
Oh.
Dude, I am...
I feel like I'm jumping the tech tree a little here.
Fucking making electron tubes?
What the fuck, brother?
That's crazy!
That's a lot!
Whoa!
Dang!
Mechanical crafter.
Deployer.
Sequenced gear shift!
Whatever the fuck that means.
Clockwork bearing optical sensor.
Controller rail.
What?
Hold on.
A unidirectional powered rail with variable speed.
Controlled by the signal strength supply to it.
Oh!
So it's like a powered rail, but I can control the speed.
I see.
That's cool.
Contraption controls!
Okay.
Smart shoot.
Velocity sensor.
Man, this is some next level crap that I just unlocked.
Wow.
Torsion spring.
What else do I have?
Wheel mount.
Didn't something else unlock as well?
Yeah.
Analog transmission.
Display board.
What the fuck?
Okay, that was nice.
That was a lot.
What do we craft first?
Let's do...
You know what?
Let's make a cauldron.
Wait, I already had a cauldron.
Now we have two cauldrons.
Shit.
Oh well.
We made a cauldron!
That was like the last thing I needed to make right now.
Mechanical...
Let's make a deployer!
Brass hand!
That's what that is for.
I guess it makes sense.
There's a little hand on it.
Casing, electron tube...
Ooh, yeah.
Let's do it.
I have casing, right?
Yep.
Boom.
Uh...
Fuck, what was the name?
Deployer.
Make it.
Ooh, we're unlocking more!
Wheels?
I guess?
Okay.
So you add wood...
To a cogwheel...
And you get a...
Large cogwheel.
Guys, don't believe those enlargement adds.
They're not real.
Sandpaper.
Oh, I can make this do that.
Add wood to a shaft and you get a cogwheel.
Thicks on wool gives me...
Envelopes.
And decides.
Right, I...
Oh!
Dude!
This is it?
My factory is complete.
Ha ha ha!
This is what I need, baby!
I need to set this up.
Okay, so we need...
Oh my...
Yo!
Can we automatically strip it as well?
We can automatically strip it as well!
Ha ha ha ha!
That's amazing.
Brass casing.
Okay, yeah.
So you can put that on.
So I...
It's like...
It's like anything I can do.
It can do.
So if I right-click something...
It can do it.
Wait.
Can it plant a seed?
Can it shear a sheep?
This...
This is huge.
This is a big one.
Okay, okay.
Hold on.
Um...
Right.
But what about the minecart shit?
Hold on.
Let me see if there's anything else I need to make that.
Because I...
I don't want to get distracted right now.
I was on a mission.
You know?
What is minecart rela...
Oh, what is this?
Oh, we need another electron tube for that.
Mechanical crafter.
I get three of them?
Why?
I guess they come in bulk?
Sequenced gear shift.
Minecart.
There's got to be something I can fucking do to...
I want to mine!
I want to mass mine.
I want to...
Somehow connect...
Minecart.
With the thingy.
You know?
Packager.
Smart fluid pipe.
Okay.
Mechanical drill.
Cart assembler?
Maybe.
Minecart?
Cart?
Give me wood.
Wait.
Minecart?
No.
Cart?
Wait, don't I have all that?
No, I don't.
No, I do.
Oh, this has to be it.
Let's see it.
Oh, no, wait.
No, no, no.
This is not it.
I've seen this one before.
Powered cart assemblers, mount attached.
Never mind.
It is.
Show me.
But this is only half...
Okay.
So, my plan is like half complete now.
The other half is...
Well, we can't go infinitely in one direction.
Except if there's...
What do you call it?
Rails.
Right?
Right.
Super glue.
Got it.
Okay.
I mean, yeah.
Actually, what I can do...
I just make a one by two hole.
You know, let's say I go really fast.
I have efficiency four or whatever on my pickaxe.
Make a large hole.
I just plop down some...
I plop down some rails.
Then at the very end, I have a minecart.
And I make sure that it like...
It covers more than the one by two.
So, it has a way to go through.
But it's still going to destroy everything around it.
You know what I mean?
So, basically, we need a big drill.
We can make this happen.
For sure.
Let me see here.
What did I...
Did I just unlock another achievement there?
With that?
Is it time?
Witness your cuckoo clock announced bedtime.
Vertical logistics.
Transport some items by chute.
Extract or insert items into a container using a funnel.
Connect two shafts with a mechanical belt.
Right.
But I want to know how to make the belt.
That's the problem.
Whoa, there's a lot of copper stuff.
Apply copper ingots to strip the wood.
Creating a waterproof casing for your machines.
Oh.
I thought it was just like a visual thing.
You know?
You can put brass.
You can put...
Andesite.
Or you can put this.
And it's just like a visual.
But I guess it also...
Unlocks new stuff.
Operate a pair of crushing wheels at maximum speed.
Speaking of maximum speed...
Still haven't fucking done this!
Let's do that now.
Right now.
We gotta focus on achievements here.
Just a little bit, I guess.
I'm not getting distracted.
This is totally the plan.
Do we have sails already?
I think we have a couple.
Can I just keep adding on to that?
I guess we'll find out.
Sail.
Sticks.
Alloy.
Oh my god.
I need my alloy though!
I can't do this.
I need my alloy.
I'm saving my alloy.
Yeah.
The next thing I'm making...
I'm gonna try and make the drill.
Because I have an idea how to do it now.
That's next on the docket.
For sure.
And you know what?
Watch this.
I'm going to do this.
Okay.
Now we needed a block on top.
Wait.
I think it needs to face the other way.
You see that arrow?
I wonder if I can use my wrench to change direction on that.
Instead of picking it up again.
Yeah!
There we go!
Wait.
Always face toward motion.
What?
Pause actors while rotating?
Just keep it standard for now, I guess?
Did it need power or something?
I thought it needed power.
Where is it?
Am I blind?
Without a redstone signal, it disas...
Sorry.
What?
Aha!
Ah!
I see.
Maybe this one?
Give me that one.
Keep it simple.
Oh, shit.
I need to...
Ah!
Come on.
Move him!
Hasta!
Okay.
Here.
Now, wrench.
It's on.
Ooh!
Look at that, baby!
And now...
Now?
Wait, also...
Ah!
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
I need to...
Shit.
Wait, how does this work?
Huh.
Let's start with one minecart for now.
Keep it simple.
Let's attach this immediately.
Ah, wait.
I think we need glue for this.
Yeah.
And then we turn it off.
Wait, how do I go opposite?
There we go.
And now?
Boom.
Disassembled.
Right?
Sweet!
You ready?
Ah, but wait a minute.
This needs to spin as well.
Hold up.
This is getting a little...
Wait a second.
This needs to...
This needs to spin.
We need some kind of...
Power source here.
Wait.
Are we gonna transport a little...
A little fucking windmill along with it?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
I'm just imagining the stupidest looking thing of all time, you know?
Let's see if it actually sticks.
Why did it turn around?
Moving with purpose.
Right.
The other way.
Go.
Wait, why is it pointing that way?
Oh, wait.
This is because...
Go.
Ow!
Oh, it hurts!
Wait, why does it hurt?
Why did that hurt?
It's not spinning.
Is it...
Huh?
Wait.
Get rid of this.
That's not needed anymore.
Fuck it.
Go.
Ow!
Why you spin?
Fucking face the other way, you idiot.
This makes no sense at all.
Makes no sense.
No.
Can you please...
There we go.
Come on.
Oh!
Wait, why...
What?
Okay, first off...
Why did it just...
Spin?
I'm so confused.
Wait a...
Wait a second.
Hold on.
Oh!
My super glue is still here!
It works!
I thought I consumed it.
That's wonderful.
It's not...
It's facing this way!
Ah, wait, wait, wait.
Maybe I need to...
Always face toward...
Motion.
But it's not doing that.
Lock rotation.
Lock that shit.
Lock it down.
This way.
And now...
There.
And...
Here.
No.
There.
Boom.
Glue.
Oh, wait!
It's already glued!
Interesting.
So, it has a memory.
Oh, that's nice.
I wasn't ready.
Put it back.
Here we go.
Maximum strength!
15.
Ah, but we also need...
Okay, I see, I see.
Obviously, we need to dig below as well.
But you see my vision, right?
So, right now, we're just gonna make a 1x2 like this way.
Like that.
And then...
Oh, but wait a minute.
Yeah, then I put down the rails, and we're fucking golden.
Unless I can somehow not do that.
Can I do it in a better way?
Let me think.
So, if I just...
Maybe it's like a thing where if it hits a mountain, it just keeps going.
You know?
Maybe they simplified it like that.
Because apparently this one is spinning, even though there's no power on it, which makes no sense.
So, I'm not quite sure what's going on there.
Um...
Definitely need more drills.
Right?
Yeah.
Okay, I'll have to think about that.
I hate this one, by the way.
I should have taken the other lever.
But I get how...
I understand how it works.
I get it now.
And it's really cool.
And I know how to harvest things from over here now.
Or here.
I know how to kill these fools.
Dude, I'm gonna make a rotating kill machine.
That's right.
You will all die by the mechanical saws.
Yes.
Or, even better.
Check it out.
Look at the floor.
Right now, it's a floor.
Right?
It's nice.
There's grass.
Actually, there's not much grass.
They ate it all.
But then I click a button.
The floor fucking rotates.
The whole floor.
And there's saws everywhere.
And they get sawed from below.
Their feet get sawed over.
And meat comes out.
And then I click it again.
And it goes back.
What do you think?
Pretty good, right?
That way, I don't have to rely on them accidentally walking into my saw.
They all get sawed.
It's the same time.
Nice.
I get it now.
Very nice.
Okay.
Use a mechanical press and a basin to create fewer items.
That one's easy.
Connect two shafts with a mechanical belt.
Kelp drive.
Fucking kelp!
That's not robbery!
Are you kidding me?
This is kelp, right?
Is that kelp?
Tell me that's it.
It's kelp.
So that's how you fucking make it!
I was like, when is this gonna show up?
You know?
But here it is.
Give me that.
18.
Dude, I have just unlocked like four things in the span of 30 minutes.
It's like record pace right now compared to normal.
Holy shit.
Okay, let's see.
I can't wait to see this one.
Uh, let me see this again.
Dried kelp?
Is that what I need?
Uh, can I not just smoke it here?
It's a smoker.
Oh!
I can totally do that!
Sick!
And we got glass too.
Not bad.
Torches.
I only have one torch right now.
Show me.
Oh my god.
Oh!
We got it, baby!
We got it.
Let me see that.
Fucking kelp.
Brass funnel.
We unlock that too?
Andesite funnel.
Tires!
So, wait.
I guess this is rubber?
Or what?
When you dry kelp, it's rubbery or something?
Mechanical belt.
It's sticky.
That's amazing.
Guys.
The industrial revolution is actually coming now.
You know what the best part about all this is?
I know how to make andesite casing.
That's like the best part.
I mean, that's good, you know?
But the thing is, I couldn't have used this without the, you know, andesite thingy.
So that's even better.
This is like, totally overwhelming right now.
Let's just put some stuff in here.
And let's click here and click there.
I have something to look forward to next time, for sure.
Oh, yeah.
Next time it's gonna be a banger, man.
We're gonna make belts!
What the fuck is going on with the chat right now?
Are you seeing what I'm seeing?
It's like...
Crashing out.
Aw, Jackie just jumped up to get a hug.
We're gonna stop that from happening.
Jackie!
No, no.
Stay here.
I meant the music.
Yeah, Jackie knows it's about food time.
That's not Jackie.
Okay, I'm just gonna let her walk free.
Whatever.
You can be whatever you want.
No, I'm not playing, so it's fine.
What do you think, guys?
Is the revolution coming?
I think the industrial revolution is here.
Isn't it?
Dude, I have all the pieces I need.
For the cranking.
The cranking will be insane.
The revolution will be televised.
I like that.
Kelp is the key.
Yes, it is!
I'm thinking next time, I'm gonna go into the ocean, and I'm gonna collect pretty much everything there is.
Jackie is rubbing her face against the microphone.
I'm sorry if you can hear that.
Jackie, no, don't do that.
There's hairs everywhere now.
And I have to de-hair the whole place now.
I wanna hear her.
Did you not hear her just now, rubbing her face against the microphone?
Oh, maybe the microphone is just not picking it up.
Who are you gonna belt first?
Uh, Isaac.
For sure.
That's the first thing I do, man, when I make that belt.
I'm gonna find Isaac, and I'm gonna punish him.
Factory must grow.
The factory is not even a factory right now.
Because I didn't have any pieces until now.
Now it's actually a factory.
Well, it's going to be a factory.
But we're gonna make a preliminary factory first.
Just so I can get the tools to make my house.
And then when I'm happy with my house, then we find a hotel.
And we steal it.
We take it with us.
The whole thing!
We bring it back home.
And we turn it into a factory.
And inside that factory, we're gonna have belts.
We're gonna have deployers.
We're gonna have mixers.
We're gonna have the whole shebang.
Yeah.
The ultimate heist.
I like it.
Isaac Newton over here.
I'm gonna steal the moon for you.
Yes.
I actually have a rope pulley.
When is next stream?
I don't know.
Whatever I feel like it.
I can't answer that question.
Probably very soon.
You know?
Let me see.
It's Friday today.
Definitely gonna play some XCOM tomorrow.
Maybe Sunday.
Most likely.
Probably Sunday, yeah.
And let me see.
So we also have next week.
So all of next week, I'm most likely gonna stream.
probably not every day, but I'm gonna stream like next week.
And then also the weekend.
And then after that, there's gonna be a little bit of a break because I'm moving.
And I need to set everything up and all that.
So, you know.
From the first to maybe the sixth or so.
Definitely lower cadence of streams.
Yeah, I'm moving into a slightly bigger place.
It's the same area.
It's just, you know, it's the same building, just a slightly bigger unit.
I got the opportunity to do it, so I'm taking it.
More room for Jackie.
Exactly.
It's gonna be way more room for Jackie.
She's gonna be able to jump all around.
And she loves running around too.
So I think she's gonna love it.
I'm gonna pack my flat with a minecart.
You're right!
And some glue.
I'm gonna glue every single moving box together and then move them all on a belt made of kelp.
Are you gonna reinstall the cat shelves too?
Of course!
I love those things and so does Jackie.
Obviously I'm gonna install those.
In fact, I may even expand on it.
I don't need a sorting system in my apartment.
I'm pretty good at sorting things in real life actually.
It's just Minecraft.
It's my weak spot, you know?
You could make a breathing apparatus out of kelp too.
I could!
We're gonna establish a beachhead and hunt them down aggressively.
I did finish Rectify.
It wasn't like super amazing towards the end.
It was barely enough to keep me going.
But it was okay.
Just join.
What have you accomplished so far?
I'm not gonna spoil it!
Let's just say I...
I did a lot, okay?
I killed it.
I really did.
I'm gonna play Subnautica too?
Yeah, when it's done.
When it's finished, I shall play it.
You can finally keep your pants up!
You're right!
Now I just need the suspenders.
Cyberpunk get on pause at some point?
Yeah.
I would say there's a 99% chance it will be unpaused at some point.
Especially because they're making a second Cyberpunk.
I mean, I have to.
I just have to.
I just don't know when.
But it will be unpaused.
99%.
But isn't Valheim done right now though?
You said it would be fun when it's done.
But that one is done, isn't it?
Wait a minute.
Is it me or is chat really delayed?
Wait, what the?
Is that just me or is chat kind of delayed?
Oh, okay.
Maybe it is just me then.
Maybe it's because...
So, I'm also streaming in 2K resolution right now.
Or 1440p technically.
Maybe that has something to do with it.
By the way, how has that been for you guys?
How does 1440p work?
Does any of you use it?
Is it a big difference?
Does it work well?
There's no problems?
Nothing like that?
Won't let me use it?
Is that because you're in a country where you can't use it?
Because I know some countries cannot at this point.
Apparently, they're rolling it out to more countries as time goes on.
You didn't even notice it was on 1440p?
I used to be in 1080p and when I would look at the VODs on Twitch just to check, it looked like ass.
And I was like, damn, is that what it looks like when I'm live?
Holy shit, that's bad.
Well, I just had to do this.
You're on 720p?
Isn't that like really blocky though and pixelated?
Twitch VOD compression?
Oh, is the VOD worse than the livestream then?
Because if that's the case, then that's good.
I mean, it's not good, but, you know, at least the livestream is not suffering.
I know it's Minecraft, but even Minecraft, you know, it does look a lot worse in low bitrate.
Yeah, it is a lot better than 1080.
Like, it is a lot more pixels you get.
And Twitch also allows you to up the bitrate to quite a bit.
Right now, it is on what is the bitrate like right now?
9,000.
9,200 and usually you can only have 6,000 on 1080.
I think it's dynamically adjusting the bitrate too, so if I were to play something very motion heavy right now, I think the bitrate would go even higher.
Yes, exactly.
Multi.
Yeah, it dips during rain and I guess snow too.
Snow is like the big offender.
Because it's like big particles and there's a lot of them.
But Minecraft snow is also insane.
Like, the whole screen is just like confetti.
It's completely over the top.
Alright, guys, I'm out of here!
Thank you so much for being here.
Checking it out with me.
I think we made a lot of good progress.
Next stream is going to be Pog, as the kids say.
Can't wait for that one.
We're going to belt it up.
It's going to be a good time.
Anyway, I'll see you around.
Have a great Friday and enjoy your weekend, okay?
That's an order.